.	O	O	#
usb	O	O	O
vxworks	O	O	O
5	O	O	O
4	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
discount	O	O	O
car	O	O	O
seat	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
crack	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
b-jigsaw	O	O	O
7.7	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
private	O	O	O
gladiators	O	O	O
cover	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
neal	neal_cavuto	O	B-PER	Neil_Cavuto	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neil_Cavuto
cavuto	O	O	I-PER
email	O	O	O
address	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cdkey	O	O	O
do	O	O	O
lotr	O	O	O
battle	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
middle	O	O	O
earth	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
poems	O	O	O
with	O	O	O
all	O	O	O
indefinite	O	O	O
pronouns	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
click4fone	click4fone	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
e	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
map	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
brighton;	brighton;_colo	O	B-LOC	Brighton,_Colorado	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brighton%2C_Colorado
colo	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
rebecca	rebecca_french	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
french	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
marion	marion_o._anderson	O	B-PER	Marion_Anderson_(politician)	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marion_Anderson_%28politician%29
o.	O	O	I-PER
anderson	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
minuclip	O	O	O
com	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
function	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
left	O	O	O
temple	O	O	O
lobe	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
brain	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
totesreich	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
playstation	O	O	O
2	O	O	O
games	O	O	O
new	O	O	O
releases	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
towns	O	O	O
located	O	O	O
""exits	O	O	O
7""	O	O	O
8	O	O	O
""new	""new_jersey""	O	B-LOC	New_jersey	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_jersey
jersey""	O	O	I-LOC
turnpike	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
revolution;fl	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
listen	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
or	O	O	O
download	O	O	O
music	O	O	O
from	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
game	O	O	O
shenmue	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
san	san_francisco	O	B-LOC	San_francisco	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/San_francisco
francisco	O	O	I-LOC
rapid	O	O	O
transit	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
melania	melania_mills	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
mills	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
remax	remax	O	B-ORG	Remax	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Remax
athens	athens	O	B-LOC	Athens	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Athens
area	O	O	O
homes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
northeastern	northeastern_brickface_&_stucco	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
brickface	O	O	I-ORG
&	O	O	I-ORG
stucco	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
office	office	O	B-ORG	Office	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Office
of	O	O	O
foreign	O	O	O
assect	O	O	O
control	O	O	O
list	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tablica	O	O	O
multimedialna	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cybrex	cybrex	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
and	O	O	O
treadmill	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bmw	bmw_bank	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
bank	O	O	I-ORG
in	O	O	O
utah	utah	O	B-LOC	Utah	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Utah
.	O	O	#
american	O	O	O
bald	O	O	O
eagle	O	O	O
picture	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
order	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
cases	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
british	O	O	O
latin	O	O	O
declension	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fixed	O	O	O
rate	O	O	O
mortgage	O	O	O
advice	O	O	O
uk	uk	O	B-LOC	Uk	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uk
.	O	O	#
compatiblity	O	O	O
horoscope	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
calculate	O	O	O
water	O	O	O
flow	O	O	O
usaf	usaf	O	B-ORG	Usaf	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Usaf
.	O	O	#
dianelaurent	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
portal	O	O	O
1311	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
catapres	O	O	O
drug	O	O	O
tts	O	O	O
patch	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bwao;mljvcszqionmkujiowertyop	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rothenberg	O	O	O
tavern	O	O	O
stein	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
me	me	O	B-ORG	Me	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Me
bath	O	O	O
icecream	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
kezia	kezia_rodriogues	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
rodriogues	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
master	O	O	O
angler	O	O	O
awards	O	O	O
mi	mi	O	B-LOC	Mi	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mi
.	O	O	#
was	O	O	O
i	O	O	O
out	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
my	O	O	O
head	O	O	O
was	O	O	O
i	O	O	O
out	O	O	O
my	O	O	O
mind?	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
philips	philips	O	B-ORG	Philips	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philips
tv	O	O	O
14t3722/3782	O	O	O
manual	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
catabolite	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
funeral	O	O	O
homes	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
clemson	clemson	O	B-LOC	Clemson_University	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clemson_University
.	O	O	#
billboard	billboard	O	B-ORG	Billboard	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Billboard
hot	O	O	O
100	O	O	O
all	O	O	O
time	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dynosour	O	O	O
coloring	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
men	O	O	O
listening	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
busy	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
bee	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
parking	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
"";""	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
""newark;nj	""newark;nj	O	B-LOC
.	O	O	#
clueless	O	O	O
moive	O	O	O
quotes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gorilla	gorilla_black	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
black	O	O	I-PER
ft.	O	O	O
mario	mario_winans	O	B-PER	Mario_Winans	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mario_Winans
winans	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
solar	O	O	O
power	O	O	O
louisiana	louisiana	O	B-LOC	Louisiana	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Louisiana
rebate	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dyno	O	O	O
label	O	O	O
prescription	O	O	O
labels	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
universal	O	O	O
brand	O	O	O
remote	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bed	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O
100%	O	O	O
mortgages	O	O	O
uk	uk	O	B-LOC	Uk	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uk
.	O	O	#
what	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
do	O	O	O
if	O	O	O
your	O	O	O
husband	O	O	O
is	O	O	O
drunk	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sarting	O	O	O
my	O	O	O
own	O	O	O
business	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
shall	O	O	O
be	O	O	O
free	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ceramic	O	O	O
crafts	O	O	O
lighting	O	O	O
home	home_depot	O	B-ORG	Home_depot	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Home_depot
depot	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
vancuover	vancuover	O	B-LOC	Vancouver	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vancouver
wa.	O	O	O
tiendas	O	O	O
mexicanas	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
a	O	O	O
how	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
guide	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
creat	O	O	O
portfolios	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dr;	dr;_james_rippe	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
james	O	O	I-PER
rippe	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
kentucky	kentucky	O	B-LOC	Kentucky	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kentucky
rifles	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
general	O	O	O
dynamics	O	O	O
uec-100	O	O	O
remote	O	O	O
control	O	O	O
head	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
binoculars	O	O	O
scorecard	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
optics4birding	optics4birding	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
apartments	O	O	O
near	O	O	O
oakland	oakland_university	O	B-ORG	Oakland_University	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oakland_University
university	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
programming	O	O	O
language	O	O	O
design	O	O	O
concepts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
leann	leann_coburn	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
coburn	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
political	O	O	O
groups/japan	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
architect	architect_association	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
association	O	O	I-ORG
ahmedabad	ahmedabad	O	B-LOC	Ahmedabad	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ahmedabad
.	O	O	#
nashville	nashville	O	B-LOC	Nashville	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nashville
physician	O	O	O
specialists	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
definition	O	O	O
horizontal	O	O	O
property	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sew	O	O	O
discounted	O	O	O
uk	uk	O	B-LOC	Uk	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uk
.	O	O	#
east	east_tennessee	O	B-LOC	East_Tennessee	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/East_Tennessee
tennessee	O	O	I-LOC
cheer	O	O	O
allstars	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
keating	keating_and_company	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
and	O	O	I-ORG
company	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
rehobeth;	rehobeth;_alabama	O	B-LOC	Rehobeth,_Alabama	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rehobeth%2C_Alabama
alabama	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
heavy	O	O	O
duty	O	O	O
shelving	O	O	O
5101t183	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dr.	dr._mike	O	B-PER	Dr._Mike	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dr._Mike
mike	O	O	I-PER
magee	magee	O	B-PER	Magee	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Magee
.	O	O	#
raid	O	O	O
3	O	O	O
versus	O	O	O
raid	O	O	O
5	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hair	O	O	O
styles	O	O	O
heavy	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
redhat	O	O	O
linux	O	O	O
xdm	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pendant	O	O	O
settings	O	O	O
&	O	O	O
supplies	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
like	O	O	O
water	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
chocolate	O	O	O
book	O	O	O
reviews	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
online	O	O	O
personal	O	O	O
trainer	O	O	O
school	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
scond	O	O	O
hans	O	O	O
buses	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bath	O	O	O
shower	O	O	O
shop	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
compress	O	O	O
chill	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ntms""	O	O	O
""north	""north_texas	O	B-ORG	North_Texas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_Texas
texas	O	O	I-ORG
microwave	microwave_society	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
society	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
e-blueprint	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mortgage	O	O	O
term	O	O	O
life	O	O	O
insurance	O	O	O
leads	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
landlord	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
tenant	O	O	O
rockville	rockville	O	B-LOC	Rockville,_Maryland	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rockville%2C_Maryland
maryland	maryland	O	B-LOC	Maryland	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maryland
.	O	O	#
steam	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
boats	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nap""	O	O	O
""non	O	O	O
authorized	O	O	O
preposition	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
demo	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
de	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
black	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
white	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
2	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
aventura	aventura	O	B-LOC	Aventura	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aventura
vacation	O	O	O
rental	O	O	O
property	O	O	O
owners	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
jean-paul	jean-paul_sartre	O	B-PER	Jean-paul_sartre	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jean-paul_sartre
sartre	O	O	I-PER
and	O	O	O
hegel	hegel	O	B-PER	Hegel	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hegel
.	O	O	#
nikon	O	O	O
series	O	O	O
e	O	O	O
lens	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pager	O	O	O
service	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
south	south_lyon_city	O	B-LOC	South_Lyon,_Michigan	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_Lyon%2C_Michigan
lyon	O	O	I-LOC
city	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
find	O	O	O
software	O	O	O
can	O	O	O
read	O	O	O
.gtd	O	O	O
file	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mister	O	O	O
sign	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cvr	O	O	O
lttr	O	O	O
examples	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
termites	O	O	O
toxic	O	O	O
humans	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
northbridge;il	northbridge;il	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
about	O	O	O
famous	O	O	O
black	O	O	O
people	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
balloon	O	O	O
fetish	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
recio	recio	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
printer	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bed	O	O	O
&	O	O	O
breakfasts	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
slovakia	slovakia	O	B-LOC	Slovakia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Slovakia
.	O	O	#
drop	O	O	O
drop	O	O	O
like	O	O	O
its	O	O	O
hot	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
metal	O	O	O
found	O	O	O
objects	O	O	O
sculpture	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
is	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
thorough	O	O	O
antecedent	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
members	O	O	O
identification	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
carbonear;newfoundland	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
short	O	O	O
stories	O	O	O
about	O	O	O
technology	O	O	O
mistakes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
shirtless	O	O	O
victor	victor_webster	O	B-PER	Victor_Webster	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Victor_Webster
webster	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
clipart	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
bapteme	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
harris	harris_martin_publishing	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
martin	O	O	I-ORG
publishing	O	O	I-ORG
conferences	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
adjustment	O	O	O
disorder	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
alcohol	O	O	O
abuse	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
songs	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
highschool	O	O	O
graduation	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
firearms	O	O	O
defensive	O	O	O
trainin	O	O	O
georgia	georgia	O	B-LOC	Georgia_(U.S._state)	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Georgia_%28U.S._state%29
.	O	O	#
mieszkania	O	O	O
na	O	O	O
sprzedaz	O	O	O
w	O	O	O
jastrzebiu	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
eastern	O	O	O
front	O	O	O
political	O	O	O
cartoons	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fishing	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
pullman	pullman	O	B-LOC	Pullman,_Chicago	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pullman%2C_Chicago
.	O	O	#
diversity	O	O	O
development	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
advance	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
""/""	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
decline	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
issues	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
real	O	O	O
estate;	O	O	O
pinole;	pinole;_ca	O	B-LOC	Pinole,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pinole%2C_California
ca	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
surfside	surfside_iv_condominiums;	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
iv	O	O	I-ORG
condominiums;	O	O	I-ORG
port	port_hueneme_ca	O	B-LOC	Port_Hueneme,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Port_Hueneme%2C_California
hueneme	O	O	I-LOC
ca	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
baptist	O	O	O
churches	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
keystone	keystone_heights_florida	O	B-LOC	Keystone_Heights,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Keystone_Heights%2C_Florida
heights	O	O	I-LOC
florida	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
causes	O	O	O
cleft	O	O	O
palette	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
marcus	marcus_garvey""	O	B-PER	Marcus_garvey	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marcus_garvey
garvey""	O	O	I-PER
america	O	O	O
world	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mens	O	O	O
warwhouse	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
drapermortuary	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fight;	O	O	O
pound	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
christianacademyofknoxville	christianacademyofknoxville	O	B-ORG	Christian_Academy_of_Knoxville	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christian_Academy_of_Knoxville
.	O	O	#
oak	O	O	O
entertainment	O	O	O
centers	O	O	O
factory	O	O	O
direct	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
aausztriaimunka	O	O	O
lieze-online	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
delutia	O	O	O
albutiu	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
leington	leington	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
medical	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ddr	O	O	O
512	O	O	O
mb	O	O	O
pc3200	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
all	O	O	O
inclusive	O	O	O
carribeaan	carribeaan	O	B-LOC	Carribean	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carribean
.	O	O	#
products	O	O	O
made	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
quartz	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
what	O	O	O
is	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
island	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
iwo	iwo_jima	O	B-LOC	Iwo_jima	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iwo_jima
jima	O	O	I-LOC
used	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
now	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chris	O	O	O
tel	O	O	O
info	O	O	O
servemp3	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
jonesville	jonesville_fish_net_co.	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
fish	O	O	I-ORG
net	O	O	I-ORG
co.	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
number	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
hurricanes	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
1985	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
body	O	O	O
health	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
mind	O	O	O
dayspa	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
johnson	johnson_city_tn	O	B-LOC	Johnson_City,_Tennessee	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Johnson_City%2C_Tennessee
city	O	O	I-LOC
tn	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
pictures	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
death	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
famous	O	O	O
people	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
elementary	O	O	O
country	O	O	O
map	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
falcon	falcon_coastal	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
coastal	O	O	I-ORG
fishing	O	O	O
rods	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
calotterypreviousnumbers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
connectitut	connectitut	O	B-LOC	Connecticut	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Connecticut
census	O	O	O
reports	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
african	O	O	O
american""	O	O	O
style	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
costume	O	O	O
slutty	O	O	O
halloween	O	O	O
idea	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
beach-camping	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
february	O	O	O
calender	O	O	O
xbox	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alfired	O	O	O
up	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
freedom	O	O	O
marina	O	O	O
pompano	O	O	O
larson	O	O	O
boats	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
description	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
chaconia	O	O	O
flower	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fo	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
calculation	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
names	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
spanish	O	O	O
panter	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
belbinscore	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
builders	O	O	O
lumber	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
hardware	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cayman	cayman_islands	O	B-LOC	Cayman_islands	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cayman_islands
islands	O	O	I-LOC
ritz	ritz_carlton	O	B-ORG	Ritz_carlton	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ritz_carlton
carlton	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
keylogger	O	O	O
removal	O	O	O
tool	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
princess	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
pea	O	O	O
historical	O	O	O
origins	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ann	ann_summers	O	B-ORG	Ann_Summers	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ann_Summers
summers	O	O	I-ORG
products	O	O	O
asp	O	O	O
gid	O	O	O
6	O	O	O
cat	O	O	O
12	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
richmond	richmond	O	B-LOC	Richmond	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richmond
ssl	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
amoxicyline	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
skyox	skyox	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
o2	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
acrolehelper	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
robitville	robitville	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
lieutenant-governor	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
quebec	quebec	O	B-LOC	Quebec	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Quebec
.	O	O	#
orlando;	orlando;_florida	O	B-LOC	Orlando,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orlando%2C_Florida
florida	O	O	I-LOC
best	O	O	O
antique	O	O	O
buys	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
heloo	O	O	O
.com	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
needing	O	O	O
love	O	O	O
from	O	O	O
father	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
red	O	O	O
eyed	O	O	O
antihistamine	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lyrics	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
karma	O	O	O
by	O	O	O
alicia	alicia_keya	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
keya	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
pipe	O	O	O
construction""	O	O	O
railroad	O	O	O
tracks	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
flashgames	O	O	O
free	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
available	O	O	O
property	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
middleburg	middleburg_heights	O	B-LOC	Middleburg_Heights	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Middleburg_Heights
heights	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
banded	O	O	O
silver	O	O	O
jewelry	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ministarstvo	O	O	O
financija	O	O	O
porezna	O	O	O
prijava	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
faxmyresume	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
twenty-first	O	O	O
amendment	O	O	O
bowdoin	O	O	O
street	O	O	O
boston	boston	O	B-LOC	Boston	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boston
.	O	O	#
saints	O	O	O
with	O	O	O
halos	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sweating	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
odour	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nero	nero	O	B-ORG	Nero	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nero
recorder	O	O	O
driver	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
first	O	O	O
guitor	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mapa	O	O	O
de	O	O	O
mexico	mexico	O	B-LOC	Mexico	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mexico
para	O	O	O
colorear	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
duty	O	O	O
gear	O	O	O
uniforms	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ana	ana_letobarone	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
letobarone	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
scarpe	O	O	O
kejo	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
motor	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
del	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
crecimiento	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
online	O	O	O
quote	O	O	O
universal	universal_life_insurance	O	B-ORG	Universal_life_insurance	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Universal_life_insurance
life	O	O	I-ORG
insurance	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
page	O	O	O
foto	O	O	O
news	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
sims2	O	O	O
bunker	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
emergency	O	O	O
dental	O	O	O
extraction	O	O	O
wilderness	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
unreleased	O	O	O
dora	dora	O	B-PER	Dora	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dora
party	O	O	O
supplies	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
new	new_york	O	B-LOC	New_york	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_york
york	O	O	I-LOC
state	O	O	O
zip	O	O	O
code	O	O	O
listings	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alle	O	O	O
betrokken	O	O	O
actoren	O	O	O
betrekken	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
het	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cathedral	cathedral_of	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
of	O	O	I-ORG
st	st_joseph	O	B-ORG	St_Joseph	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/St_Joseph
joseph	O	O	I-ORG
in	O	O	O
jefferson	jefferson_city;	O	B-LOC	Jefferson_City	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jefferson_City
city;	O	O	I-LOC
mo	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
apples	O	O	O
quick	O	O	O
view	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
golf	O	O	O
club	O	O	O
making	O	O	O
lmformation	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
baguio	baguio_city	O	B-LOC	Baguio_City	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baguio_City
city	O	O	I-LOC
property	O	O	O
taxes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dwayne	dwayne_haught	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
haught	O	O	I-PER
austin	austin	O	B-PER	Austin	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Austin
.	O	O	#
pk\lay	O	O	O
now	O	O	O
msn	msn	O	B-ORG	MSN	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MSN
games	O	O	O
online	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ravena	ravena	O	B-LOC	Ravena	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ravena
italy	italy	O	B-LOC	Italy	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Italy
jazz	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
murfreesboro;	murfreesboro;	O	B-LOC	Murfreesboro,_Tennessee	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Murfreesboro%2C_Tennessee
tn	O	O	O
photos	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
medications	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
problems	O	O	O
with	O	O	O
gi	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
butterfly	O	O	O
noro	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
exercise	O	O	O
furniture	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
blue	O	O	O
s	O	O	O
clue	O	O	O
live	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
st	st_louis_minesota	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
louis	O	O	I-LOC
minesota	O	O	I-LOC
apartments	O	O	O
furnished	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
dark	O	O	O
louts	O	O	O
pod	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
jd	O	O	O
marketing""	O	O	O
australia	australia	O	B-LOC	Australia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Australia
.	O	O	#
chris	chris_jones	O	B-PER	Chris_Jones	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chris_Jones
jones	O	O	I-PER
(wr)	O	O	O
{jsu}	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
outdoor	O	O	O
garage	O	O	O
lights	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
stroke	O	O	O
billy	billy_squire	O	B-PER	Billy_Squire	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Billy_Squire
squire	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
ghs""	O	O	O
""great	O	O	O
hair	O	O	O
styles	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alaska	alaska	O	B-LOC	Alaska	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alaska
joe	joe	O	B-PER	Joe	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joe
.	O	O	#
bought	O	O	O
groceries	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
stream""	O	O	O
language:en	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ojay	O	O	O
italy	italy	O	B-LOC	Italy	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Italy
.	O	O	#
van	van_gigh	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
gigh	O	O	I-PER
still	O	O	O
lifes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
a4	O	O	O
letterhead	O	O	O
size	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tim	tim_white	O	B-PER	Tim_White	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tim_White
white	O	O	I-PER
&	O	O	O
morning	O	O	O
song	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sahara	sahara	O	B-ORG	Sahara	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sahara
s2618	O	O	O
projector	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
comphimset.	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
panoramic	O	O	O
photo	O	O	O
prints	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
todays	O	O	O
dynamic	O	O	O
businesses	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sailor	O	O	O
moon	O	O	O
r	O	O	O
legend	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
negamoon	O	O	O
pictures	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
street	O	O	O
rod	O	O	O
jag	O	O	O
exhaust	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
seaworld	seaworld	O	B-LOC	Seaworld	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seaworld
cheap	O	O	O
hotels	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bristol	bristol	O	B-LOC	Bristol	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bristol
racing	O	O	O
cars	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
college	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
computer	O	O	O
science	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cnbc	cnbc	O	B-ORG	Cnbc	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cnbc
and	O	O	O
valentines	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
day	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
coleman	O	O	O
expedition	O	O	O
cookware	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
painting	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
inside	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
your	O	O	O
house	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
author	O	O	O
harris	harris	O	B-PER	Harris	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Harris
.	O	O	#
patricia	patricia_mckillip	O	B-PER	Patricia_Mckillip	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Patricia_Mckillip
mckillip	O	O	I-PER
biography	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rumors	O	O	O
about	O	O	O
aaron	aaron_carter	O	B-PER	Aaron_carter	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aaron_carter
carter	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
th350	O	O	O
valve	O	O	O
body	O	O	O
bolts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
missouri	missouri	O	B-LOC	Missouri	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Missouri
motorcycle	O	O	O
trike	O	O	O
dealers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dennis;ma	dennis;ma	O	B-LOC	Dennis,_Massachusetts	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dennis%2C_Massachusetts
hotels	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bartley's	bartley's_burgers	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
burgers	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
new	new_york	O	B-LOC	New_york	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_york
york	O	O	I-LOC
aip	aip	O	B-ORG	Aeronautical_Information_Publication	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aeronautical_Information_Publication
.	O	O	#
baby	O	O	O
guinea	O	O	O
pig	O	O	O
photos	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dr.	O	O	O
steven	steven_symes	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
symes	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
roller	O	O	O
ronks	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
service	O	O	O
myidentityprotectionplan	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tanning	O	O	O
feet	O	O	O
hands	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
romantic	O	O	O
mexican	O	O	O
resturants	O	O	O
minnesota	minnesota	O	B-LOC	Minnesota	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Minnesota
.	O	O	#
mci	mci	O	B-ORG	Mci	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mci
on	O	O	O
my	O	O	O
verizon	verizon	O	B-ORG	Verizon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Verizon
bill	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
service	O	O	O
not	O	O	O
available	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
genuine	O	O	O
louis	louis_vuitton	O	B-ORG	Louis_vuitton	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Louis_vuitton
vuitton	O	O	I-ORG
handbags	O	O	O
discounted	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pictures	O	O	O
facts	O	O	O
""fourth	O	O	O
planet""	O	O	O
sun	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
letter	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
black	O	O	O
ashe	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
allison	allison_kurtis_clarkston	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
kurtis	O	O	I-PER
clarkston	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
ofpublishing	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
consumer	O	O	O
reports	O	O	O
auto	O	O	O
polish	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
children	O	O	O
christmas	O	O	O
songs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nick	nick_gavin	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
gavin	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
royal	O	O	O
decamarin	O	O	O
nuevo	O	O	O
vallarta	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
altinay	O	O	O
gesundheit	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
los	los_angeles	O	B-LOC	Los_angeles	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Los_angeles
angeles	O	O	I-LOC
water	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
power	O	O	O
boil	O	O	O
order	O	O	O
notice	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
breast	O	O	O
cancer	O	O	O
usa	usa	O	B-LOC	Usa	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Usa
.	O	O	#
newton	O	O	O
valve	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
camping	O	O	O
rv	O	O	O
accessories	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hudsun	O	O	O
train	O	O	O
csx	O	O	O
dvd	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pioneer	pioneer	O	B-ORG	Pioneer	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pioneer
kh-8811	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
stuff	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
do;sacramento	do;sacramento	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
asme	O	O	O
a350	O	O	O
lf2	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rochesternychat	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
probowl	O	O	O
scoring	O	O	O
history	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
caesar	O	O	O
rodney's	O	O	O
ride	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bilfinger	bilfinger_berger_ag;	O	B-ORG	Bilfinger_Berger	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bilfinger_Berger
berger	O	O	I-ORG
ag;	O	O	I-ORG
germany	germany	O	B-LOC	Germany	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Germany
.	O	O	#
shower/tub	O	O	O
enclosure	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nut	O	O	O
cert	O	O	O
gun	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dallas	dallas	O	B-LOC	Dallas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dallas
lubbock	O	O	O
drivetime	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
johnson	johnson	O	B-PER	Johnson	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Johnson
(coupling)	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
shreik	O	O	O
coloring	O	O	O
sheets	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
web	O	O	O
flight	O	O	O
booking	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
verizon	verizon	O	B-ORG	Verizon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Verizon
white	O	O	O
residential	O	O	O
pages	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
new	new_jersey	O	B-LOC	New_jersey	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_jersey
jersey	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
butterfly	O	O	O
rose	O	O	O
tattoos	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lupus	lupus_production	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
production	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
michael	michael_cullighan	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
cullighan	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
rogers	rogers_corners;	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
corners;	O	O	I-LOC
michigan	michigan	O	B-LOC	Michigan	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michigan
.	O	O	#
glencoe	O	O	O
science	O	O	O
nerve	O	O	O
cells	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
furniture	O	O	O
stores	O	O	O
chaises	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
new	new_york	O	B-LOC	New_york	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_york
york	O	O	I-LOC
vs	O	O	O
belton	belton	O	B-LOC	Belton	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Belton
.	O	O	#
fox	fox_5	O	B-ORG	WTTG	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WTTG
5	O	O	I-ORG
wasington	wasington_dc	O	B-LOC	Washington,_D.C.	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Washington%2C_D.C.
dc	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
collection	O	O	O
service	O	O	O
bur	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
capgemini	O	O	O
2005	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
white	O	O	O
fluffy	O	O	O
frosting	O	O	O
icing	O	O	O
recipe	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
event	O	O	O
organiser	O	O	O
perkawinan	perkawinan	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
rehabiltiation	O	O	O
centers	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
northern	northern_virginia	O	B-LOC	Northern_Virginia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northern_Virginia
virginia	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
csg""	O	O	O
""combinatorial	O	O	O
solid	O	O	O
geometric	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
aluminum	O	O	O
cupcake	O	O	O
papers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
foia	O	O	O
regarding	O	O	O
dead	O	O	O
service	O	O	O
members'	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
e	O	O	O
library	O	O	O
big	O	O	O
chalk	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pictures	O	O	O
""star	O	O	O
trek""	O	O	O
characters	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rear	O	O	O
lexus	lexus	O	B-ORG	Lexus	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lexus
car	O	O	O
shades	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
continuing	O	O	O
medical	O	O	O
education	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
otolaryngologists	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rustburg	O	O	O
va	O	O	O
real	O	O	O
estate	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
david	david_tubb	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
tubb	O	O	I-PER
air	O	O	O
force	O	O	O
pilot	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
what	O	O	O
is	O	O	O
""closed	O	O	O
loop""	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
dld	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
perkembangan	O	O	O
islam	O	O	O
di	O	O	O
cina	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
enlarged	O	O	O
uterus	O	O	O
constant	O	O	O
urination	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nfl	nfl	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
squares	O	O	O
calculator	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
eli	eli_pariser	O	B-PER	Eli_Pariser	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eli_Pariser
pariser	O	O	I-PER
bio	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
what	O	O	O
is	O	O	O
promotional	O	O	O
research?	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
michigan	michigan_stat_university_law_school	O	B-ORG	Michigan_State_University_College_of_Law	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michigan_State_University_College_of_Law
stat	O	O	I-ORG
university	O	O	I-ORG
law	O	O	I-ORG
school	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
patterson	patterson	O	B-PER	Patterson	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Patterson
lakers	lakers	O	B-ORG	Lakers	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lakers
.	O	O	#
birthday	O	O	O
party	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
kids	O	O	O
at	O	O	O
rock	rock_city	O	B-ORG	Rock_City	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rock_City
city	O	O	I-ORG
notts	notts	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
aa	O	O	O
world	O	O	O
conference	O	O	O
toronto	toronto	O	B-LOC	Toronto	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toronto
.	O	O	#
neural	O	O	O
or	O	O	O
noise	O	O	O
or	O	O	O
synthesizer	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
colorado	colorado_springs	O	B-LOC	Colorado_Springs	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Colorado_Springs
springs	O	O	I-LOC
airprot	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
first	O	O	O
african	O	O	O
american	O	O	O
us	O	O	O
fighter	O	O	O
plait	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
i	O	O	O
whant	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
see	O	O	O
pattis	O	O	O
emele	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
lizzie	O	O	O
mcguire	O	O	O
movie	O	O	O
games	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
simon	simon	O	B-ORG	Simon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Simon
managed	O	O	O
properties	O	O	O
kansas	kansas	O	B-LOC	Kansas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kansas
.	O	O	#
new	new_york	O	B-LOC	New_York	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_York
york	O	O	I-LOC
state	O	O	O
audio	O	O	O
contest	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
digitaldruck	O	O	O
sublimieren	O	O	O
tricks	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
first	O	O	O
commercial	O	O	O
valentine's	O	O	O
day	O	O	O
cards	O	O	O
sold	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
office	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
xp;crack	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ocean	O	O	O
marine	marine_research	O	B-ORG	Marine_research	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marine_research
research	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
listing	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
commonly	O	O	O
used	O	O	O
army	O	O	O
ribbons	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alaska	alaska	O	B-LOC	Alaska	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alaska
wireless	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O
service	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
map	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
cebu	cebu	O	B-LOC	Cebu	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cebu
.	O	O	#
alaska	alaska	O	B-LOC	Alaska	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alaska
grizzly	O	O	O
record	O	O	O
man	O	O	O
eater	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
non-profit	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
texas	texas	O	B-LOC	Texas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Texas
and	O	O	O
start-up	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hot	O	O	O
room	O	O	O
remodeling	O	O	O
ideas	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
daniel	daniel	O	B-PER	Daniel	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daniel
champion	O	O	O
ruth	ruth_harris	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
harris	O	O	I-PER
lyme	O	O	O
ct	ct	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
pressure	O	O	O
change	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
ears	O	O	O
due	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
altitude	O	O	O
changes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ordering	O	O	O
cloverdale	cloverdale	O	B-LOC	Cloverdale	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cloverdale
summer	O	O	O
sausage	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pga	pga	O	B-ORG	PGA	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PGA
certified	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dob	O	O	O
teloscopes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
washington	washington	O	B-LOC	Washington	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Washington
soldiers	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
iraq	iraq	O	B-LOC	Iraq	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iraq
.	O	O	#
mom's	O	O	O
house	O	O	O
toledo	toledo	O	B-LOC	Toledo,_Spain	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toledo%2C_Spain
.	O	O	#
usb	O	O	O
front	O	O	O
panel	O	O	O
adapter	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ffit	O	O	O
kids	O	O	O
buderim	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
teen	O	O	O
titans/picturs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bestbuy	O	O	O
appleton	appleton_wi	O	B-LOC	Appleton,_Wisconsin	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Appleton%2C_Wisconsin
wi	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
elizabeth	elizabeth_filbrun	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
filbrun	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
seed	O	O	O
money	O	O	O
business	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gif	O	O	O
images	O	O	O
royalty	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
arleen	arleen_gill	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
gill	O	O	I-PER
qualcom	qualcom	O	B-ORG	Qualcomm	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Qualcomm
.	O	O	#
hard	O	O	O
rock	O	O	O
cd's	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
seabrook	seabrook_island_real_estate	O	B-ORG	Seabrook,_Texas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seabrook%2C_Texas	NONE	NONE
island	O	O	I-ORG
real	O	O	I-ORG
estate	O	O	I-ORG
seabrook	seabrook_texas	O	B-LOC
texas	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
new	new_york	O	B-LOC	New_york	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_york
york	O	O	I-LOC
transit	O	O	O
connection	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
foie	O	O	O
gros	O	O	O
animal	O	O	O
rights	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
remodeling	O	O	O
around	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
chimney	O	O	O
inside	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
house	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
blue	O	O	O
giant	O	O	O
pallet	O	O	O
jack	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cheap	O	O	O
flights	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
cyprus	cyprus	O	B-LOC	Cyprus	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cyprus
.	O	O	#
tests	O	O	O
results	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
medical	O	O	O
assistants	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
saucesage	O	O	O
product	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
michigan	michigan	O	B-LOC	Michigan	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michigan
theaters	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cartoon	O	O	O
programs	O	O	O
1965-1980	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
national	O	O	O
observed	O	O	O
health	O	O	O
days	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
college	O	O	O
humor	O	O	O
every	O	O	O
nintendo	O	O	O
game	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nyyankeesjackets	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lyrics	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
hypnotise	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
montana	montana_city	O	B-LOC	Montana_City,_Montana	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Montana_City%2C_Montana
city	O	O	I-LOC
mt	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
real	O	O	O
estate	O	O	O
agents	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
storage	storage_usa	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
usa	O	O	I-ORG
telephone	O	O	O
number	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ardenwood	ardenwood_farm	O	B-LOC	Ardenwood_Farm	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ardenwood_Farm
farm	O	O	I-LOC
in	O	O	O
fremont	fremont	O	B-LOC	Fremont,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fremont%2C_California
.	O	O	#
v$session	O	O	O
view	O	O	O
account	O	O	O
sys	O	O	O
system	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hair	O	O	O
dye	O	O	O
labels	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
meeting	O	O	O
spaces;	O	O	O
portland	portland_or	O	B-LOC	Portland,_Oregon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Portland%2C_Oregon
or	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
hand	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
tattoos	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cartiel	cartiel_jewlery	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
jewlery	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
diary	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
ann	ann_frank	O	B-PER	Anne_Frank	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anne_Frank
frank	O	O	I-PER
book	O	O	O
report	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
od	O	O	O
interventions	O	O	O
free	O	O	O
cases	O	O	O
pdf	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
what	O	O	O
ot	O	O	O
feed	O	O	O
iguanas	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
avon	avon	O	B-ORG	Avon_Products	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Avon_Products
trkey	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
facts	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
canary	canary_islands	O	B-LOC	Canary_islands	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canary_islands
islands	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
quangle	O	O	O
net	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
maincoons	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
va	va	O	B-LOC	Va	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Va
.	O	O	#
biltmore	biltmore_wstate	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
wstate	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
female	O	O	O
dogs	O	O	O
humping	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
auto	auto_fast_inc	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
fast	O	O	I-ORG
inc	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
mississippi	mississippi	O	B-LOC	Mississippi	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mississippi
graduation	O	O	O
requirements	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
de	O	O	O
jeweled	O	O	O
game	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cheesecake	O	O	O
chocolate	O	O	O
mint	O	O	O
chip	O	O	O
recipe	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ati	O	O	O
radeon	O	O	O
9600	O	O	O
tx	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
are	O	O	O
there	O	O	O
any	O	O	O
spanish	O	O	O
airlines	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cake	cake	O	B-ORG	Cake	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cake
brand	O	O	O
handbags	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
give	O	O	O
me	O	O	O
some	O	O	O
examples	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
puzzles	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
salvage	O	O	O
auction	O	O	O
sacramento	sacramento	O	B-LOC	Sacramento	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sacramento
.	O	O	#
brake	O	O	O
press	O	O	O
machinery	O	O	O
technology	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
faccacia	O	O	O
bread	O	O	O
recipe	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rate	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
increase	O	O	O
formula	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
complication	O	O	O
rates	O	O	O
with	O	O	O
esophogeal	O	O	O
dilitation	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
frand	frand_james	O	B-PER	Frank_James	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Frank_James
james	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
volvo	O	O	O
repair	O	O	O
mobile	mobile	O	B-LOC	Mobile,_Alabama	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mobile%2C_Alabama
alabama	alabama	O	B-LOC	Alabama	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alabama
.	O	O	#
roll	O	O	O
pan	O	O	O
led	O	O	O
lights	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cholesterol	O	O	O
diet	O	O	O
high	O	O	O
patient	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
oklahoma	oklahoma	O	B-LOC	Oklahoma	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oklahoma
christian	O	O	O
women's	O	O	O
conference	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
redding	redding	O	B-ORG	Redding	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Redding
relaty	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
max	O	O	O
torque	O	O	O
driven	O	O	O
pulley	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
city	city_of_parksville	O	B-LOC	Parksville,_British_Columbia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Parksville%2C_British_Columbia
of	O	O	I-LOC
parksville	O	O	I-LOC
stats	stats	O	B-LOC	Stats	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stats
.	O	O	#
due	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
february	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
death	O	O	O
faulkner	faulkner	O	B-PER	William_Faulkner	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Faulkner
.	O	O	#
until	O	O	O
now	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
marketing	O	O	O
literature	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
loyalty	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
how	O	O	O
much	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
john	john_cenas	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
cenas	O	O	I-PER
belt	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lyricsonnet	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
map	O	O	O
quest/forest	O	O	O
servicewashington	O	O	O
state	state	O	B-LOC	State	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/State
.	O	O	#
daytona	daytona	O	B-ORG	Daytona	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daytona
media	O	O	O
player	O	O	O
audio	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
kubota	kubota	O	B-ORG	Kubota	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kubota
b21serial	O	O	O
numbers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
picture	O	O	O
egress	O	O	O
basement	O	O	O
window	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chip	chip_carter_son	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
carter	O	O	I-PER
son	O	O	I-PER
of	O	O	O
jimmy	jimmy_carter	O	B-PER	Jimmy_Carter	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jimmy_Carter
carter	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
dakota	O	O	O
vinyl	O	O	O
siding	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
nj	nj	O	B-LOC	New_Jersey	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Jersey
.	O	O	#
rhinestone	O	O	O
skirt	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chuttney	O	O	O
music	O	O	O
charts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
montague	montague_street	O	B-LOC	Montague_Street,_London	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Montague_Street%2C_London
street	O	O	I-LOC
florist	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
comparativo	O	O	O
xeon	O	O	O
p4	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
romantic	O	O	O
compatilbility	O	O	O
test	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ncaa	ncaa	O	B-ORG	Ncaa	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ncaa
basketball	O	O	O
rule	O	O	O
changes	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
2004-2005	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
massachusetts	massachusetts	O	B-LOC	Massachusetts	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Massachusetts
1040ez	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ms	O	O	O
huntsville	huntsville	O	B-LOC	Huntsville	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Huntsville
walk	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mattoon	mattoon	O	B-LOC	Mattoon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mattoon
school	school_district;	O	B-LOC	School_district	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/School_district
district;	O	O	I-LOC
illinois	illinois	O	B-LOC	Illinois	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Illinois
.	O	O	#
shord	O	O	O
fish	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hravinly	O	O	O
ham	O	O	O
ypsilanti	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
start	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
graphic	O	O	O
designer	O	O	O
business	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
donavan	donavan_darious	O	B-PER	Donovin_Darius	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donovin_Darius
darious	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
sierra	O	O	O
cat	O	O	O
mouse	O	O	O
puzzle	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
olt""	O	O	O
""on	O	O	O
line	O	O	O
transaction	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
new	O	O	O
constraction	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
what	O	O	O
were	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
olypics	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
athens	athens	O	B-LOC	Athens	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Athens
greece	greece	O	B-LOC	Greece	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greece
played	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
listing	O	O	O
career	O	O	O
goals	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gemini	O	O	O
10""	O	O	O
revolution	O	O	O
ring	O	O	O
saw	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
causes	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
abnormal	O	O	O
rise	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
body	O	O	O
temperature	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hospitals	O	O	O
chicagoland	chicagoland	O	B-LOC	Chicagoland	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicagoland
.	O	O	#
seyxygirles	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
accuring	O	O	O
rotary	O	O	O
tables	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
maxtor	O	O	O
hard	O	O	O
drive""	O	O	O
retailer	O	O	O
reseller	O	O	O
australia	australia	O	B-LOC	Australia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Australia
.	O	O	#
malpractice	O	O	O
lawyers	O	O	O
north	north_carolina	O	B-LOC	North_carolina	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_carolina
carolina	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
calciprivia	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fondos	O	O	O
de	O	O	O
pantalla	O	O	O
de	O	O	O
los	O	O	O
looney	O	O	O
toons	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
philosophy	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
proximate	O	O	O
cause	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
downloda	O	O	O
dvdsoftwgere	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
motherbords	O	O	O
drivers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
objektif	O	O	O
teleperubatan	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bikes;	O	O	O
go	O	O	O
carts	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
unique	O	O	O
cartoon	O	O	O
dollmakers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
schools	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
deharadun	deharadun	O	B-LOC	Dehradun	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dehradun
.	O	O	#
audiovoxportable12.1'lcd	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
apw	apw_school_district	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
school	O	O	I-ORG
district	O	O	I-ORG
phone	O	O	O
numbers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
reviews	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
hotel	O	O	O
aragon	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
csun	O	O	O
master	O	O	O
programs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
boston	boston_harbor	O	B-LOC	Boston_harbor	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boston_harbor
harbor	O	O	I-LOC
tugs	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
towig	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dialysis	O	O	O
jobs	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
atalnta	atalnta_ga	O	B-LOC	Atlanta	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Atlanta
ga	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
mpg	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
canyons	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
healthy	O	O	O
weight	O	O	O
loss	O	O	O
plans	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
women	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
miss""	O	O	O
pageant	O	O	O
hair	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
figure	O	O	O
total	O	O	O
number	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O
accumulated	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
menards	menards	O	B-ORG	Menards	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Menards
spokesman	O	O	O
ray	ray_szmanda	O	B-PER	Ray_Szmanda	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ray_Szmanda
szmanda	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
funny	O	O	O
suite	O	O	O
backgrounds	O	O	O
wallpapers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
orange	orange_peel	O	B-ORG	Orange_peel	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orange_peel
peel	O	O	I-ORG
""asheville	""asheville	O	B-LOC	Asheville	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Asheville
north	north_carolina	O	B-LOC	North_carolina	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_carolina
carolina	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
hallcraft	hallcraft_industries	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
industries	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
crop	crop_in_style	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
in	O	O	I-ORG
style	O	O	I-ORG
products	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
falcon	falcon_bluffs_middle_school	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
bluffs	O	O	I-ORG
middle	O	O	I-ORG
school	O	O	I-ORG
rankings	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
county	county_of_parkland	O	B-ORG	Parkland_County,_Alberta	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Parkland_County%2C_Alberta
of	O	O	I-ORG
parkland	O	O	I-ORG
school	school	O	B-ORG	School	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/School
division	O	O	O
alberta	alberta	O	B-LOC	Alberta	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alberta
.	O	O	#
bbmac	bbmac	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
fan	O	O	O
net	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mwr	O	O	O
nsa	nsa	O	B-LOC	National_Security_Agency	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Security_Agency
new	new_orleans	O	B-LOC	New_Orleans	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Orleans
orleans	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
colangila	O	O	O
flower	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
city	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
montgomery""	montgomery""	O	B-LOC	Montgomery,_Alabama	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Montgomery%2C_Alabama
alabama	alabama	O	B-LOC	Alabama	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alabama
ordinances	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
signs	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
crones	O	O	O
disease	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tpti	O	O	O
ofertas	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
clarksville	clarksville_ar	O	B-LOC	Clarksville,_Arkansas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clarksville%2C_Arkansas
ar	O	O	I-LOC
-	O	O	O
auto	O	O	O
dealers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ontario	ontario	O	B-LOC	Ontario	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ontario
police	O	O	O
chief	O	O	O
1989	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
married	O	O	O
english	O	O	O
females	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sentiments	O	O	O
list	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ncaa	O	O	O
football	O	O	O
2005	O	O	O
""free	O	O	O
strategy	O	O	O
guide	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
new	new_york	O	B-LOC	New_york	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_york
york	O	O	I-LOC
singing	O	O	O
lessons	O	O	O
children	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
choppers	O	O	O
inc.	O	O	O
window	O	O	O
decals	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gas	O	O	O
match	O	O	O
hk	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mortgage	O	O	O
ammaturization	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
industrial	O	O	O
revolution	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
america	america	O	B-LOC	America	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/America
1850-1900	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fasting	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
4	O	O	O
days	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
weather	O	O	O
los	los_angeles	O	B-LOC	Los_Angeles	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Los_Angeles
angeles	O	O	I-LOC
december	O	O	O
27;	O	O	O
2005	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
electron	O	O	O
net	O	O	O
easy	O	O	O
test	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tlc	O	O	O
finding	O	O	O
new	O	O	O
gierl	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mrs.	mrs._fraziers	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
fraziers	O	O	I-PER
first	O	O	O
grade	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
intraocular	O	O	O
lymphoma	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
combustion	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
gas	O	O	O
engine	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
intranets	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
projecting	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
roi	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cherokee	O	O	O
burn	O	O	O
permit	O	O	O
georgia	georgia	O	B-LOC	Georgia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Georgia
.	O	O	#
atsc	O	O	O
qam	O	O	O
tuner	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
music	O	O	O
et	O	O	O
clips	O	O	O
videos	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ages	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
teens	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
hurricane	O	O	O
disasters	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pontaiac	O	O	O
convertibles	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
custimizable	O	O	O
team	O	O	O
jerseys	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
uzalenienia	O	O	O
medialne	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mini	O	O	O
sombraro	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
semi	O	O	O
truck	O	O	O
battier	O	O	O
charger	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ftp	O	O	O
exploror	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
miami	miami	O	B-LOC	Miami	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Miami
private	O	O	O
transportation	O	O	O
children	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tesco	tesco	O	B-ORG	Tesco	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tesco
dvd	O	O	O
rental	O	O	O
uk	uk	O	B-LOC	Uk	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uk
.	O	O	#
cerca	O	O	O
agenzia	O	O	O
del	O	O	O
territorio	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
palmpal	O	O	O
signature	O	O	O
capture	O	O	O
tablet	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
montessorischoolinshreveport	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
krell	krell	O	B-ORG	Krell	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Krell
blown	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mag	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
eyes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
powerpuff	O	O	O
girls	O	O	O
as	O	O	O
teens	O	O	O
that	O	O	O
had	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
contest	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
turf	O	O	O
supplies	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
hunter	hunter_valley	O	B-LOC	Hunter_Valley	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hunter_Valley
valley	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
kohler	kohler	O	B-ORG	Kohler	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kohler
k3262-1	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
days	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
our	O	O	O
lives;	O	O	O
shane	shane_&_kimberley_donovan	O	B-PER	Shane_Donovan_and_Kimberly_Brady	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shane_Donovan_and_Kimberly_Brady
&	O	O	I-PER
kimberley	O	O	I-PER
donovan	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
broown	O	O	O
book	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
voli	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
pescara	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
parigi	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
accoville	accoville_wv	O	B-LOC	Accoville,_West_Virginia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Accoville%2C_West_Virginia
wv	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
atlantishealth	O	O	O
plan;com	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pajama	O	O	O
day	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
kindergarten	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
premanufactured	O	O	O
homes	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
midwest	midwest	O	B-LOC	Midwestern_United_States	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Midwestern_United_States
.	O	O	#
photos	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
florida's	florida's	O	B-LOC	Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida
intracostal	O	O	O
waterways	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
uncomplex	O	O	O
ptsd	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
photos	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
rusian	O	O	O
airplane	O	O	O
bodys	O	O	O
death	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
firmware	O	O	O
200r	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
marsanomalies	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
merceray	O	O	O
out	O	O	O
board	O	O	O
engins	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alcoholanonymous	alcoholanonymous	O	B-ORG	Alcoholics_Anonymous	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alcoholics_Anonymous
in	O	O	O
me	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
floating	O	O	O
boat	O	O	O
northeast	northeast	O	B-LOC	Northeast	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northeast
.	O	O	#
project	O	O	O
tek-tip	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sore	O	O	O
throat""	O	O	O
rash	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
starbucks	starbucks	O	B-ORG	Starbucks	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Starbucks
global	O	O	O
oppurtinaty	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
division	O	O	O
three	O	O	O
power	O	O	O
rankings	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
drum	O	O	O
stool""	O	O	O
setup	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
find	O	O	O
me	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
truth	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
const	O	O	O
urea	O	O	O
major	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
broadband	O	O	O
chicago;	chicago;	O	B-LOC	Chicago	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicago
il	il	O	B-LOC	Illinois	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Illinois
.	O	O	#
eruption	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
volcano	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bruges	bruges_belgium	O	B-LOC	Bruges	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bruges
belgium	O	O	I-LOC
bed	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
breakfasts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
beading	O	O	O
out	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
norm	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
could	O	O	O
adapt	O	O	O
their	O	O	O
working	O	O	O
style	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
theirs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
studio	O	O	O
apartments	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
northern	northern_ave	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
ave	O	O	I-LOC
in	O	O	O
phoenix	phoenix	O	B-LOC	Phoenix	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phoenix
.	O	O	#
lo-carb	O	O	O
cheesecake	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
concept	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
office	O	O	O
administrator	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
medium	O	O	O
length	O	O	O
messy	O	O	O
hairstyles	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
printable	O	O	O
angel	O	O	O
pcitrues	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
time	O	O	O
machine	O	O	O
blue	O	O	O
prints	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nswgovernment	nswgovernment_school_system	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
school	O	O	I-ORG
system	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
casual	O	O	O
dinnette	O	O	O
furniture	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
what	O	O	O
is	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
jeep	O	O	O
grand	O	O	O
cherokee	O	O	O
wiring	O	O	O
harness	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
men's	O	O	O
clothing	O	O	O
short	O	O	O
sizes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
scores	O	O	O
wednesday	O	O	O
feb	O	O	O
9	O	O	O
pm	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
asian	O	O	O
restaurants	O	O	O
appleton	appleton_wi	O	B-LOC	Appleton,_Wisconsin	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Appleton%2C_Wisconsin
wi	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
carson	carson_city	O	B-LOC	Carson_City	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carson_City
city	O	O	I-LOC
nv	nv	O	B-LOC	Nv	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nv
rental	O	O	O
homes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
university	university_of_maryland	O	B-ORG	University_Of_Maryland	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/University_Of_Maryland
of	O	O	I-ORG
maryland	O	O	I-ORG
law	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
student	student	O	B-ORG	Student	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Student
reviews	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
piantumazione	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
saturay	O	O	O
night	O	O	O
live	O	O	O
air	air_supply	O	B-ORG	Air_supply	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Air_supply
supply	O	O	I-ORG
kattan	kattan	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
sawmills	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
canada	canada	O	B-LOC	Canada	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canada
.	O	O	#
emma	emma	O	B-PER	Emma	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Emma
but	O	O	O
lon	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
larma	larma	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
boots	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
painting	O	O	O
verses	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
walls	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
anorexcia	O	O	O
south	south_africa	O	B-LOC	South_africa	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_africa
africa	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
element	O	O	O
name	O	O	O
list;forms;frames;color	O	O	O
asp	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
poorest	O	O	O
countries	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
carribean	carribean	O	B-LOC	Caribbean	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Caribbean
.	O	O	#
cadena	O	O	O
alimentica	O	O	O
de	O	O	O
los	O	O	O
animales	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
crocheted	O	O	O
rug	O	O	O
making	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
connecticut	connecticut	O	B-LOC	Connecticut	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Connecticut
infant	O	O	O
fun	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
presari	O	O	O
6412us	O	O	O
memory	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
crx	O	O	O
superride	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
muppet	O	O	O
treasure	O	O	O
island	O	O	O
movie	O	O	O
clips	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bomb	O	O	O
glass	O	O	O
tabel	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
personaltiy	O	O	O
sketch	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
texas	texas_homeland_security	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
homeland	O	O	I-ORG
security	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
elixer	O	O	O
xerox	xerox	O	B-ORG	Xerox	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Xerox
.	O	O	#
should	O	O	O
i	O	O	O
use	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
cover	O	O	O
letter	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
resume	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
plattwrmer	O	O	O
sei	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pacheco	pacheco_california	O	B-LOC	Pacheco,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pacheco%2C_California
california	O	O	I-LOC
realtor	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
health	O	O	O
risks	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
old	O	O	O
cemeteries	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
republican	republican_party	O	B-ORG	Republican_party	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Republican_party
party	O	O	I-ORG
in	O	O	O
louisiana	louisiana	O	B-LOC	Louisiana	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Louisiana
.	O	O	#
acting	O	O	O
like	O	O	O
crazy	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
i	O	O	O
saw	O	O	O
jim	jim_reeves	O	B-PER	Jim_Reeves	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jim_Reeves
reeves	O	O	I-PER
up	O	O	O
there	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cadencecentral	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
arranger	O	O	O
peter	peter_blair	O	B-PER	Peter_Blair	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter_Blair
blair	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
saintfrancesuniversity	saintfrancesuniversity	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
forescenic	O	O	O
science	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pictures	O	O	O
astasia	O	O	O
euglenoids	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rowlett	rowlett_chamber_of_commerce	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
chamber	O	O	I-ORG
of	O	O	I-ORG
commerce	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
only_one	O	O	O
921	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bupbe_khongtinhyeu777	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ohio	ohio	O	B-LOC	Ohio	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ohio
laws	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
divorce	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
osx	O	O	O
dvd	O	O	O
backup	O	O	O
decrypter	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dj	O	O	O
steilio	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
oriental	O	O	O
back	O	O	O
yard	O	O	O
landscapes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
paintballequipmentin	O	O	O
tampa	tampa	O	B-LOC	Tampa,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tampa%2C_Florida
.	O	O	#
how	O	O	O
do	O	O	O
lynxes	O	O	O
see?	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
std	O	O	O
slides;	O	O	O
pictures	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
table	O	O	O
2001	O	O	O
rates	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fortune	fortune_lounge_players_club	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
lounge	O	O	I-ORG
players	O	O	I-ORG
club	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
salvation	salvation_army	O	B-ORG	Salvation_army	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Salvation_army
army	O	O	I-ORG
drug	O	O	O
rehab	O	O	O
san	san_fransisco	O	B-LOC	San_Fransisco	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/San_Fransisco
fransisco	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
mail	O	O	O
hcbe	O	O	O
net	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
building	O	O	O
460	O	O	O
performance	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
maishadwilliams	maishadwilliams	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
weather	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
average	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
temperatures	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rollabout	O	O	O
scooter	O	O	O
chair	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
american	american_union_life_insurance	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
union	O	O	I-ORG
life	O	O	I-ORG
insurance	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
apartment	O	O	O
houses	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
rent	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
online	O	O	O
classes;	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
old	O	O	O
crock	O	O	O
pots	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
keyless	O	O	O
remote	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
1998	O	O	O
honda	O	O	O
accord	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
furinture	O	O	O
entertaiment	O	O	O
ceters	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
allied	allied	O	B-ORG	Allied	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Allied
beachwood	beachwood_ohio	O	B-LOC	Beachwood,_Ohio	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beachwood%2C_Ohio
ohio	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
facts	O	O	O
about	O	O	O
cezanne	cezanne	O	B-PER	Cezanne	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cezanne
.	O	O	#
hacks	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
scripts	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
solutions	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
monika	monika_sanches	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
sanches	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
della	O	O	O
conferenza	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
so	O	O	O
yestoday	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
equipment	equipment_direct_sales_inc	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
direct	O	O	I-ORG
sales	O	O	I-ORG
inc	O	O	I-ORG
ma	ma	O	B-LOC	Massachusetts	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Massachusetts
.	O	O	#
henryk	henryk	O	B-PER	Henryk	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Henryk
and	O	O	O
liefelt	liefelt	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
books	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
friction	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
louden	louden	O	B-LOC	Louden	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Louden
county;virginia	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pfs	O	O	O
or	O	O	O
dvd's	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hatch	O	O	O
reacter1/2	O	O	O
finger	O	O	O
rappel	O	O	O
gloves	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
macrannall	macrannall	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
multi-level	O	O	O
hand	O	O	O
tools	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
saint	saint_louis	O	B-LOC	St._Louis,_Missouri	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/St._Louis%2C_Missouri
louis	O	O	I-LOC
marti	O	O	O
gras	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
melbourne	melbourne_it	O	B-ORG	Melbourne_IT	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Melbourne_IT
it	O	O	I-ORG
mission	O	O	O
control	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mriram	mriram_mcdonald	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
mcdonald	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
entertainment	O	O	O
banner;	banner;	O	B-LOC	Banner	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Banner
mississippi	mississippi	O	B-LOC	Mississippi	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mississippi
.	O	O	#
disable	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
edit	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
function	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
explorer	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
animated	O	O	O
""george	""george_w_bush	O	B-PER	George_w_bush	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_w_bush
w	O	O	I-PER
bush	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
marine	O	O	O
cerulpa	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
danvers	danvers_ymca	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
ymca	O	O	I-ORG
after	O	O	O
school	O	O	O
program	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cabins	O	O	O
oakfield	oakfield_maine	O	B-LOC	Oakfield,_Maine	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oakfield%2C_Maine
maine	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
film	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
rhinocros	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
ionesco	ionesco	O	B-PER	Eugne_Ionesco	NONE
.	O	O	#
brek	O	O	O
over	O	O	O
light	O	O	O
poles	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fbise	O	O	O
date	O	O	O
sheet	O	O	O
ssc	O	O	O
p	O	O	O
2	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
halton	halton_city	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
city	O	O	I-LOC
engine	O	O	O
stands	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
melissa	melissa	O	B-PER	Melissa	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Melissa
carpenter/realtor	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
shelves	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
computer	O	O	O
display	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mililani	O	O	O
hawaii	hawaii	O	B-LOC	Hawaii	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hawaii
mold	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
clayton	clayton_homes	O	B-ORG	Clayton_Homes	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clayton_Homes
homes	O	O	I-ORG
savannnah	savannnah	O	B-LOC	Savannah	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Savannah
.	O	O	#
flagstaff	flagstaff_arizona	O	B-LOC	Flagstaff_arizona	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flagstaff_arizona
arizona	O	O	I-LOC
tourism	O	O	O
information	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
discount	O	O	O
weddingd	O	O	O
dresss	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
disney's	disney's	O	B-ORG	The_Walt_Disney_Company	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Walt_Disney_Company
reses	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
secure	O	O	O
mini-storage	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
locate	O	O	O
train	O	O	O
stores	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ciba	ciba_vision	O	B-ORG	Ciba_Vision	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ciba_Vision
vision	O	O	I-ORG
mississaugua	mississaugua_canada	O	B-LOC	Mississauga	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mississauga
canada	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
magellan	O	O	O
road	O	O	O
atlas	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
evil	evil_kenivel	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
kenivel	O	O	I-PER
houston	houston	O	B-LOC	Houston	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Houston
.	O	O	#
preventing	O	O	O
hiv	O	O	O
positive	O	O	O
transmission	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
for	O	O	O
me	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
live	O	O	O
is	O	O	O
christ	christ	O	B-PER	Christ	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christ
for	O	O	O
youth	O	O	O
groups	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
frames	O	O	O
truck	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
car	O	O	O
rentals	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
turtle	turtle_island_fiji	O	B-LOC	Turtle_Island	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Turtle_Island
island	O	O	I-LOC
fiji	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
northwest;	O	O	O
inc.;	O	O	O
kitchen	O	O	O
timer	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
arches	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
windows	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ostherholm	ostherholm	O	B-PER	Osterholm	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Osterholm
dangerous	O	O	O
flu	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
goat	O	O	O
website	O	O	O
background	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
crown	crown_plaza	O	B-LOC	Crown_plaza	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crown_plaza
plaza	O	O	I-LOC
of	O	O	O
indianapolis	indianapolis_in	O	B-LOC	Indianapolis_IN	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indianapolis_IN
in	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
page	O	O	O
deal	O	O	O
cancun	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
counterdigits	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cream	O	O	O
cheese	O	O	O
pie	O	O	O
dough	O	O	O
recipe	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
teaching	O	O	O
license	O	O	O
nevada	nevada	O	B-LOC	Nevada	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nevada
.	O	O	#
valley	valley_greene_apts.	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
greene	O	O	I-ORG
apts.	O	O	I-ORG
wissahickon	wissahickon	O	B-LOC	Wissahickon_Creek	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wissahickon_Creek
.	O	O	#
liturgical	O	O	O
calender	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
add-a-veyor	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sealcoating	O	O	O
materials	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fratello's	fratello's_restaurant	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
restaurant	O	O	I-ORG
in	O	O	O
manchester;	manchester;_nh	O	B-LOC	Manchester,_New_Hampshire	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Manchester%2C_New_Hampshire
nh	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
dress	O	O	O
""united	O	O	O
methodist""	O	O	O
lergy	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gmc	gmc	O	B-ORG	GMC_(automobile)	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/GMC_%28automobile%29
van	O	O	O
bumper	O	O	O
parts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
denver;colorado's	denver;colorado's	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
zipcode	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tunics	O	O	O
weather	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dyi	O	O	O
fish	O	O	O
tank	O	O	O
filters	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
eclipse	O	O	O
reader	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
oyster	O	O	O
fest	O	O	O
2005;	O	O	O
atlanta;ga	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ucla	ucla_school_of_economics	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
school	O	O	I-ORG
of	O	O	I-ORG
economics	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
funny	O	O	O
voicemails	O	O	O
messages	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
phillipine	phillipine	O	B-LOC	Phillipine	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phillipine
newsftoken=43668050	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
estimated	O	O	O
total	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
dogs	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
world	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
large	O	O	O
redheads	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sample	O	O	O
projects	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
read	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
john	john_deere	O	B-ORG	John_Deere	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Deere
deere	O	O	I-ORG
electrical	O	O	O
generator	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
all	O	O	O
brands	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
deodorant	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
romantic	O	O	O
oregon	oregon	O	B-LOC	Oregon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oregon
lodging	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
serial	O	O	O
processing	O	O	O
&	O	O	O
parallel	O	O	O
processing	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
honda	honda	O	B-ORG	Honda	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Honda
off	O	O	O
road	O	O	O
bike	O	O	O
acc	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
proper	O	O	O
tire	O	O	O
installation	O	O	O
guide	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
counting	counting_crows	O	B-ORG	Counting_crows	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Counting_crows
crows	O	O	I-ORG
big	O	O	O
yellow	O	O	O
taxi	O	O	O
clip	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
electrical	O	O	O
job	O	O	O
traveler	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
teen	O	O	O
guage	O	O	O
clips	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lsu	lsu_hepatology_clinic;	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
hepatology	O	O	I-LOC
clinic;	O	O	I-LOC
william	william_cassidy	O	B-PER	William_Cassidy	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Cassidy
cassidy	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
photography	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
human	O	O	O
rights	O	O	O
development	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lyrics	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
""bet	O	O	O
you	O	O	O
can't	O	O	O
get	O	O	O
it	O	O	O
like	O	O	O
me	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chum	chum	O	B-ORG	Chum	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chum
and	O	O	O
tv	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
top	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
""40""	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
countdown	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
couty	couty	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
clerk	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
jackson	jackson_county_oregon	O	B-LOC	Jackson_County,_Oregon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jackson_County%2C_Oregon
county	O	O	I-LOC
oregon	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
emg-81	O	O	O
pickups	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
leupold	leupold	O	B-ORG	Leupold	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leupold
compass	O	O	O
range	O	O	O
finder	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
captain	captain_shyguy	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
shyguy	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
bbc	bbc	O	B-ORG	Bbc	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bbc
ni	O	O	O
news	O	O	O
broadcasters	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
north	north_dakota	O	B-LOC	North_dakota	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_dakota
dakota	O	O	I-LOC
under	O	O	O
age	O	O	O
drinking	O	O	O
laws	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
longatude	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
latidude	O	O	O
map	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
canada	canada	O	B-LOC	Canada	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canada
.	O	O	#
fagler	fagler_beach	O	B-LOC	Flagler_Beach,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flagler_Beach%2C_Florida
beach	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
mark	mark_martin	O	B-PER	Mark_Martin	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_Martin
martin	O	O	I-PER
test""	O	O	O
car	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bluecross	O	O	O
blueshield	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
orlando	orlando	O	B-LOC	Orlando,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orlando%2C_Florida
.	O	O	#
tv	O	O	O
commercial	O	O	O
air	air_force	O	B-ORG	Air_force	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Air_force
force	O	O	I-ORG
bomber	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ddb	O	O	O
706539	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
frigate	O	O	O
look	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
clogged	O	O	O
croatoid	O	O	O
arteries	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fox	fox_racing	O	B-ORG	Fox_Racing	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fox_Racing
racing	O	O	I-ORG
mx	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
children	O	O	O
hospitals	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
state	state_of_arkansas	O	B-LOC	State_of_Arkansas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/State_of_Arkansas
of	O	O	I-LOC
arkansas	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
antonello	antonello_salis	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
salis	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
neuropsychological	O	O	O
test	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
children	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
long	O	O	O
time	O	O	O
lovin	O	O	O
you	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pain	O	O	O
with	O	O	O
kidney	O	O	O
cyts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pictues	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
hemisphere	O	O	O
figures	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
outer	outer_limits_offshore	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
limits	O	O	I-ORG
offshore	O	O	I-ORG
boats	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mike	mike_smith_toyota	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
smith	O	O	I-ORG
toyota	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
books	O	O	O
with	O	O	O
rates	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
what	O	O	O
coleges	O	O	O
prepare	O	O	O
you	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
paleontology?	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
assessment	O	O	O
education	O	O	O
illinois	illinois	O	B-LOC	Illinois	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Illinois
.	O	O	#
basic	O	O	O
allowance	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
subst	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mason	mason	O	B-LOC	Mason	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mason
city""	O	O	O
""zip	O	O	O
code	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rhode	rhode_island	O	B-LOC	Rhode_island	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rhode_island
island	O	O	I-LOC
camping	O	O	O
rv	O	O	O
show	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
harley	harley_davidson	O	B-ORG	Harley_davidson	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Harley_davidson
davidson	O	O	I-ORG
gift	O	O	O
bags	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
provident	provident_trust	O	B-ORG	Provident_Life_&_Trust_Company	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Provident_Life_%26_Trust_Company
trust	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
ad	O	O	O
hoc	O	O	O
polymorphism	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
anderson	anderson	O	B-ORG	Anderson	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anderson
continuing	O	O	O
education""	O	O	O
website	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
prepare	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
job	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
restaurants/hagerstown	restaurants/hagerstown_md	O	B-LOC	Hagerstown,_Maryland	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hagerstown%2C_Maryland
md	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
estaurant	O	O	O
reviews	O	O	O
long	long_island	O	B-LOC	Long_island	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Long_island
island	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
stone	stone_tree_golf	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
tree	O	O	I-ORG
golf	O	O	I-ORG
novato	novato	O	B-LOC	Novato,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Novato%2C_California
.	O	O	#
bumble	O	O	O
bee	O	O	O
kisses	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
trinity	trinity_united_methodist_church	O	B-ORG	Trinity_United_Methodist_Church	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trinity_United_Methodist_Church
united	O	O	I-ORG
methodist	O	O	I-ORG
church	O	O	I-ORG
gainesville	gainesville	O	B-LOC	Gainesville,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gainesville%2C_Florida
.	O	O	#
robert	robert_burns	O	B-PER	Robert_Burns	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Burns
burns	O	O	I-PER
notable	O	O	O
holiday	O	O	O
song	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cheap	O	O	O
attraction	O	O	O
tickets	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
boy	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
miniskirt	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
msn	O	O	O
explorer	O	O	O
sends	O	O	O
pictures	O	O	O
with	O	O	O
red	O	O	O
x's	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fireplace	O	O	O
""wrought	O	O	O
iron""	O	O	O
accents	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mic""	O	O	O
""manufacturer	O	O	O
identification	O	O	O
code	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lightning	O	O	O
dub	O	O	O
holywood	holywood	O	B-LOC	Holywood	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Holywood
.	O	O	#
albuquerque	albuquerque	O	B-LOC	Albuquerque	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Albuquerque
child	O	O	O
safety	O	O	O
store	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mil-std	O	O	O
1399	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
david	david_deatherage;	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
deatherage;	O	O	I-PER
ks	ks	O	B-LOC	Ks	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ks
.	O	O	#
concert	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
video	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
squarepusher	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
streaming	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nicole	nicole_lyn	O	B-PER	Nicole_Lyn	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nicole_Lyn
lyn	O	O	I-PER
deliver	O	O	O
us	O	O	O
from	O	O	O
eva	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
prince	prince_edward_island""	O	B-LOC	Prince_edward_island	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prince_edward_island
edward	O	O	I-LOC
island""	O	O	I-LOC
abortion	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chicharrones	O	O	O
peruanos	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
black	O	O	O
womens	O	O	O
feet	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
legs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ridgid	O	O	O
535m	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dr	dr_william_sears;	O	B-PER	William_Sears_(physician)	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Sears_%28physician%29
william	O	O	I-PER
sears;	O	O	I-PER
attatchment	O	O	O
parenting	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
remx	O	O	O
kicks	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
price	price_pfister	O	B-ORG	Price_Pfister	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Price_Pfister
pfister	O	O	I-ORG
georgetown	georgetown	O	B-LOC	Georgetown	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Georgetown
.	O	O	#
charlie	charlie_pride	O	B-PER	Charlie_Pride	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Charlie_Pride
pride	O	O	I-PER
bioraphy	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
credit	credit_suisse	O	B-ORG	Credit_Suisse	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Credit_Suisse
suisse	O	O	I-ORG
capital	O	O	O
appreciation	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bayhibe	bayhibe	O	B-LOC	Bayahibe	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bayahibe
divin	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hotel	hotel	O	B-ORG	Hotel	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hotel
bonsai	bonsai_etape	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
etape	O	O	I-ORG
avignon	avignon	O	B-LOC	Avignon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Avignon
.	O	O	#
career	career_associates	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
associates	O	O	I-ORG
18411	O	O	O
torrance	torrance	O	B-LOC	Torrance,_Ontario	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Torrance%2C_Ontario
.	O	O	#
eric	eric_marciano	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
marciano	O	O	I-PER
radar	O	O	O
gauge	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lobster	O	O	O
tails	O	O	O
hpw	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
cook	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
eye	O	O	O
exam	O	O	O
template	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
qcam	O	O	O
310	O	O	O
drive	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
modesto	modesto_raiders	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
raiders	O	O	I-ORG
ralph	ralph_dapaah	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
dapaah	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
lorco	O	O	O
new	O	O	O
haven	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
artists	O	O	O
skulls	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
losangelascahotels.	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
performance	O	O	O
chip	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
1999	O	O	O
chevy	O	O	O
cavalier	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
usgs	usgs	O	B-ORG	United_States_Geological_Survey	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_Geological_Survey
water	O	O	O
quality	O	O	O
laboratory	O	O	O
lakewood;	lakewood;_colorado	O	B-LOC	Lakewood,_Colorado	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lakewood%2C_Colorado
colorado	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
file	O	O	O
transfer	O	O	O
methods	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
martoch	O	O	O
program	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
performance	O	O	O
grand	O	O	O
am	O	O	O
parts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sidewalk	sidewalk_pizza	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
pizza	O	O	I-ORG
sacramento	sacramento	O	B-LOC	Sacramento	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sacramento
california	california	O	B-LOC	California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/California
.	O	O	#
cat	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
heaven	O	O	O
painting	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ringwood	ringwood	O	B-LOC	Ringwood	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ringwood
nj""	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
weather	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
history	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
release	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
air	O	O	O
jordans	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
domestic	O	O	O
discipline	O	O	O
digest	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
walkthrous	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
boktai	O	O	O
2	O	O	O
solar	O	O	O
boy	O	O	O
django	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
splolzdravpoist	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
top	O	O	O
caribien	caribien	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
resorts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
insects	O	O	O
classifications	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
black	black_oak_ranch	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
oak	O	O	I-LOC
ranch	O	O	I-LOC
arkansas	arkansas	O	B-LOC	Arkansas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arkansas
.	O	O	#
prior	O	O	O
cabinet	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
joanne	joanne	O	B-PER	Joanne	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joanne
and	O	O	O
rodger	rodger_thompson	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
thompson	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
myrtle	myrtle_beach""	O	B-LOC	Myrtle_Beach,_South_Carolina	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Myrtle_Beach%2C_South_Carolina
beach""	O	O	I-LOC
""entertainment	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cavoticlus	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
abilene	abilene_aviation_school	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
aviation	O	O	I-ORG
school	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
double	O	O	O
bottom	O	O	O
line	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ata	ata_airlines	O	B-ORG	Ata_Airlines	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ata_Airlines
airlines	O	O	I-ORG
1800number	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
southern	O	O	O
baptist	O	O	O
convenstion	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
map	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
santa	santa_clarita	O	B-LOC	Santa_Clarita,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Santa_Clarita%2C_California
clarita	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
law	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
terror	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
direction	O	O	O
locator	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ficus	O	O	O
species	O	O	O
research	O	O	O
papers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
richard	richard_g._butler	O	B-PER	Richard_G._Butler	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richard_G._Butler
g.	O	O	I-PER
butler	O	O	I-PER
invented	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
train	O	O	O
alarm	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dr.	O	O	O
flame	O	O	O
window	O	O	O
tint	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
korn	korn	O	B-ORG	Korn	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Korn
6-string	O	O	O
tabs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sparkyyates2000	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
van	van_heerden_safaris""	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
heerden	O	O	I-ORG
safaris""	O	O	I-ORG
namibia	namibia	O	B-LOC	Namibia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Namibia
.	O	O	#
vikes3	O	O	O
ops	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
forest	O	O	O
penetrator	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
definition	O	O	O
disaster	O	O	O
intelligence	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
cosmetology	O	O	O
clip	O	O	O
art	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nagano	nagano_japan	O	B-LOC	Nagano,_Nagano	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nagano%2C_Nagano
japan	O	O	I-LOC
hyatt	hyatt	O	B-ORG	Hyatt	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hyatt
.	O	O	#
kryonchatphoto	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
condo	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
rent	O	O	O
by	O	O	O
owner	O	O	O
florida	florida	O	B-LOC	Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida
.	O	O	#
v	O	O	O
day	O	O	O
springfield	springfield_ma	O	B-LOC	Springfield_ma	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Springfield_ma
ma	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
renton;	renton;_washington	O	B-LOC	Renton,_Washington	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Renton%2C_Washington
washington	O	O	I-LOC
post	O	O	O
o9ffice	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
laser	O	O	O
printing	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
vancouver	vancouver_british_columbia	O	B-LOC	Vancouver_British_Columbia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vancouver_British_Columbia
british	O	O	I-LOC
columbia	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
dr.	O	O	O
arthure	arthure_lipper	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
lipper	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
purchase	O	O	O
agreement	O	O	O
new	O	O	O
home	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
richmond	richmond	O	B-LOC	Richmond	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richmond	Richmond_va	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richmond_va
ob-gyn	ob-gyn_assoc	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
assoc	O	O	I-ORG
richmond	richmond_va	O	B-LOC
va	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
stock	O	O	O
option""	O	O	O
profits	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
kellys	kellys_bleachers	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
bleachers	O	O	I-ORG
windlake	windlake	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
morris	morris_curello	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
curello	O	O	I-PER
website	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mclain	mclain_distributors	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
distributors	O	O	I-ORG
new	new_hampshire	O	B-LOC	New_Hampshire	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Hampshire
hampshire	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
christopher	christopher_paul	O	B-PER	Christopher_Paul	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christopher_Paul
paul	O	O	I-PER
curtis's	O	O	O
contributions	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
met	met	O	B-PER	Met	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Met
and	O	O	O
michael	michael	O	B-PER	Michael	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michael
and	O	O	O
vartan	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
at	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fimco	fimco	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
atv	O	O	O
sprayers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dr.	dr._thomas_ryan	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
thomas	O	O	I-PER
ryan	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
houston	houston	O	B-LOC	Houston	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Houston
biotechnology	O	O	O
industry	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cwla	cwla	O	B-ORG	CWLA	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/CWLA
national	O	O	O
conference	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
vlsi	O	O	O
symposium	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
japan	japan	O	B-LOC	Japan	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Japan
.	O	O	#
pictures	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
alender	O	O	O
pope	pope	O	B-PER	Pope	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pope
.	O	O	#
slick	O	O	O
rick	O	O	O
""the	O	O	O
show	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nmu	nmu	O	B-ORG	NMU	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/NMU
carpool	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
american	american_red_cross	O	B-ORG
red	O	O	I-ORG
cross	O	O	I-ORG
j""ean	j""ean_b._clifton	O	B-PER
b.	O	O	I-PER
clifton	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
option	O	O	O
p	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
l	O	O	O
calculation	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
blue	O	O	O
print	O	O	O
symbols	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
karoake	O	O	O
music	O	O	O
by	O	O	O
ray	ray_boltz	O	B-PER	Ray_boltz	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ray_boltz
boltz	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
harvey	harvey_mudd_college;	O	B-ORG	Harvey_Mudd_College	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Harvey_Mudd_College
mudd	O	O	I-ORG
college;	O	O	I-ORG
claremont	claremont	O	B-LOC	Claremont	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Claremont
.	O	O	#
bankruptsy	O	O	O
homes	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
mansfield	mansfield_ohio	O	B-LOC	Mansfield,_Ohio	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mansfield%2C_Ohio
ohio	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
website	O	O	O
designers;	O	O	O
3rd	O	O	O
party	O	O	O
integration	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
like	O	O	O
everyday	O	O	O
was	O	O	O
passing	O	O	O
by	O	O	O
so	O	O	O
slow	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
radisson	radisson	O	B-ORG	Radisson	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Radisson
near	O	O	O
port	port_canaveral	O	B-LOC	Port_Canaveral	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Port_Canaveral
canaveral	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
