.	O	O	#
prism	O	O	O
aha	O	O	O
cpr	O	O	O
training	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
building	O	O	O
materials	O	O	O
donation	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
osd	osd	O	B-ORG	On-screen_display	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/On-screen_display
acquisition	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
faq	O	O	O
site:jaz-.com	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
florida	florida	O	B-LOC	Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida
dmv	dmv	O	B-ORG	DMV	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DMV
license	O	O	O
check	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
very	O	O	O
hunger	O	O	O
caterpilliar	O	O	O
by	O	O	O
eric	eric_carle	O	B-PER	Eric_Carle	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eric_Carle
carle	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
mount	mount_horeb	O	B-LOC	Mount_Horeb	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Horeb
horeb	O	O	I-LOC
imp	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
carpet	O	O	O
cleaning;seattrle	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
paint	O	O	O
strokes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
movie	O	O	O
hitchhikers	O	O	O
guide	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
galaxy	galaxy	O	B-LOC	Galaxy	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Galaxy
.	O	O	#
diamond	O	O	O
o	O	O	O
campground	O	O	O
information	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
locations	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
section	O	O	O
8	O	O	O
housing	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
pg	pg_county_md	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
county	O	O	I-LOC
md	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
printable	O	O	O
kids	O	O	O
devotions	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
riedell	O	O	O
122	O	O	O
adkates	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
psichanalalyse	O	O	O
mythologie	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
spleen/sarcoidosis	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
give	O	O	O
me	O	O	O
private	O	O	O
company	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
taiwan	taiwan	O	B-LOC	Taiwan	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Taiwan
.	O	O	#
icu	O	O	O
updates	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cardiopathie	O	O	O
congenitale	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bctv	bctv	O	B-ORG	BCTV	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BCTV
wayne	wayne_cox	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
cox	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
sourcherry	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
davies	davies_gates	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
gates	O	O	I-ORG
garden	O	O	O
made	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rare	O	O	O
rose	O	O	O
pictures	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mercedes	mercedes_benz	O	B-ORG	Mercedes_benz	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mercedes_benz
benz	O	O	I-ORG
c240	O	O	O
weight	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hp	O	O	O
designjet	O	O	O
paper	O	O	O
falling	O	O	O
into	O	O	O
tray	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
eposn	O	O	O
stylus	O	O	O
color	O	O	O
740	O	O	O
not	O	O	O
printing	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sell	O	O	O
used	O	O	O
dolls	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
atlas	atlas_copco	O	B-ORG	Atlas_Copco	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Atlas_Copco
copco	O	O	I-ORG
""service	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
boat	O	O	O
from	O	O	O
west	west_plam_beach	O	B-LOC	West_Palm_Beach,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/West_Palm_Beach%2C_Florida
plam	O	O	I-LOC
beach	O	O	I-LOC
florida	florida	O	B-LOC	Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida
to	O	O	O
the	the_bahamas	O	B-LOC	The_Bahamas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Bahamas
bahamas	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
citybank	citybank	O	B-ORG	Citibank	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Citibank
credit	O	O	O
cardlost	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
charge	O	O	O
rate	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
getting	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
tongue	O	O	O
ring	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
philipiines	philipiines	O	B-LOC	Philippines	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philippines
food	O	O	O
recipe	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lhs	O	O	O
liverpool	liverpool	O	B-LOC	Liverpool	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Liverpool
k12	O	O	O
ny	ny	O	B-LOC	New_York	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_York
us	O	O	O
lhs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
beauty	O	O	O
studio;myscene	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
haywood	haywood_county;	O	B-LOC	Haywood_County	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haywood_County
county;	O	O	I-LOC
tennessee;	tennessee;	O	B-LOC	Tennessee	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tennessee
chamber	chamber_of_commerce	O	B-ORG	Chamber_of_commerce	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chamber_of_commerce
of	O	O	I-ORG
commerce	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
positive	O	O	O
consumer	O	O	O
focus	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
mental	O	O	O
health	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
okaloosa	okaloosa_county	O	B-LOC	Okaloosa_County	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Okaloosa_County
county	O	O	I-LOC
marriage	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cleaning	O	O	O
task	O	O	O
work	O	O	O
sheet	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sicclan;net	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
faq	O	O	O
site:x2g7.com	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
seachbox-earth	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
school	O	O	O
bus	O	O	O
wreak	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
grayson	grayson	O	B-LOC	Grayson	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grayson
.	O	O	#
carpet	O	O	O
outlets	O	O	O
new	new_york	O	B-LOC	New_york	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_york
york	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
tom	tom	O	B-ORG	Tom	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tom
trakers	O	O	O
blade	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
shot	O	O	O
satuday	O	O	O
05	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
philadelphia	philadelphia	O	B-LOC	Philadelphia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philadelphia
billboard	O	O	O
ordinances	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
buy	O	O	O
new	O	O	O
16mm	O	O	O
film	O	O	O
video	O	O	O
camera	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
uganda	uganda	O	B-LOC	Uganda	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uganda
loan	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
change	O	O	O
your	O	O	O
life	O	O	O
move	O	O	O
your	O	O	O
stuff	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ludwig	O	O	O
scale	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chicago	chicago	O	B-LOC	Chicago	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicago
bob	bob_nelson	O	B-PER	Bob_Nelson_(comedian)	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bob_Nelson_%28comedian%29
nelson	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
eagle	eagle_cycle	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
cycle	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
semolina	semolina_north_dakota	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
north	O	O	I-LOC
dakota	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
life-time	O	O	O
education	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sd""	O	O	O
""staunch	O	O	O
defend	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
love	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
daytime	O	O	O
dramas	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
belanger	belanger	O	B-ORG	Belanger	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Belanger
plumbing	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
used	O	O	O
lift	O	O	O
tables	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cinema	O	O	O
5	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
squamish	squamish	O	B-LOC	Squamish	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Squamish
.	O	O	#
artict	O	O	O
furr	O	O	O
seal	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
freeware	O	O	O
trayicon	O	O	O
beta	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
spiritual	O	O	O
translation	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
aya	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cascade	cascade_high_school	O	B-ORG	Cascade_High_School_(Everett,_Washington)	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cascade_High_School_%28Everett%2C_Washington%29
high	O	O	I-ORG
school	O	O	I-ORG
and	O	O	O
everett	everett	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
english	O	O	O
reports	O	O	O
about	O	O	O
epic	O	O	O
stories	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
obituary	O	O	O
william	william_hanley	O	B-PER	William_Hanley	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Hanley
hanley	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
cultural	O	O	O
strategy	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
experiment	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
terror	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
domador	O	O	O
campus	O	O	O
instancias	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
play	O	O	O
mancala	O	O	O
game	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
berostar	berostar_hotels	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
hotels	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
blue	blue_creek_marine	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
creek	O	O	I-ORG
marine	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
innova	O	O	O
qrs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
desmond	desmond_mcdaniel	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
mcdaniel	O	O	I-PER
(finney	(finney_high_school)	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
high	O	O	I-ORG
school)	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
how	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
slide	O	O	O
baseball	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bbeter	O	O	O
byers	O	O	O
women	O	O	O
or	O	O	O
men	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lady	lady_irwin_school	O	B-ORG	Lady_Irwin_School	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lady_Irwin_School
irwin	O	O	I-ORG
school	O	O	I-ORG
delhi	delhi	O	B-LOC	Delhi	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Delhi
.	O	O	#
negative	O	O	O
impact	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
enviornment	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
locate	O	O	O
consignment	O	O	O
stores	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dell	dell	O	B-ORG	Dell	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dell
latitude	O	O	O
cpi	O	O	O
266	O	O	O
mhz	O	O	O
pii	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
california	california	O	B-LOC	California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/California
road	O	O	O
condition	O	O	O
cameras	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rev.	rev._kenton_rogers	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
kenton	O	O	I-PER
rogers	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
us	us	O	B-ORG	Us	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Us
gov	O	O	O
harp	O	O	O
project	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
extreme	O	O	O
gymnastics	O	O	O
nebraska	nebraska	O	B-LOC	Nebraska	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nebraska
.	O	O	#
photos	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
spragga	spragga	O	B-PER	Spragga_Benz	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spragga_Benz
.	O	O	#
rotax	rotax_277	O	B-ORG	Rotax_277	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rotax_277
277	O	O	I-ORG
ultralight	O	O	O
engines	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lynx	O	O	O
outdoor	O	O	O
grills	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
movie	O	O	O
title	O	O	O
keyword	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
booklet	O	O	O
georgia	georgia	O	B-LOC	Georgia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Georgia
income	O	O	O
tax	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ogniwa	O	O	O
agrobiznesu	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
likin	likin_park	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
park	O	O	I-ORG
music	O	O	O
video	O	O	O
samplers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
trident	trident_real_estate	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
real	O	O	I-ORG
estate	O	O	I-ORG
hiltonhead	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
used	O	O	O
car	O	O	O
byers	O	O	O
guide	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
element	O	O	O
skateboard	O	O	O
backrounds	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
leonard	leonard_cohen	O	B-PER	Leonard_cohen	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leonard_cohen
cohen	O	O	I-PER
photo	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
greenhouse	O	O	O
designes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
microsoft	microsoft	O	B-ORG	Microsoft	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microsoft
and	O	O	O
encryption	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
base	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
requirements	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
educators	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
advantagse	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
disadvantages	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
cellular	O	O	O
telephone	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bank	bank_of	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
of	O	O	I-ORG
nova	nova	O	B-ORG	Nova	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nova
scotia/halifax	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
undeniably	O	O	O
you	O	O	O
(jeff	O	O	O
savage	O	O	O
mix)	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
my	O	O	O
computerf:\	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mecruy	mecruy	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
boat	O	O	O
engins	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
stearns	stearns_county	O	B-LOC	Stearns_County	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stearns_County
county	O	O	I-LOC
court	O	O	O
admin	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chosing	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
right	O	O	O
ipaq	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
comtempo	O	O	O
paper	O	O	O
goods	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
part	O	O	O
time	O	O	O
jobs	O	O	O
ga	ga	O	B-LOC	Georgia_(U.S._state)	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Georgia_%28U.S._state%29
.	O	O	#
delco	delco	O	B-ORG	Delco	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Delco
radio	O	O	O
rhode	rhode_island	O	B-LOC	Rhode_island	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rhode_island
island	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
dolphin	dolphin_fittness_club	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
fittness	O	O	I-ORG
club	O	O	I-ORG
new	new_york_city	O	B-LOC	New_york_city	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_york_city
york	O	O	I-LOC
city	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
haulmark	haulmark_trailers	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
trailers	O	O	I-ORG
mcadoo	mcadoo	O	B-LOC	McAdoo,_Pennsylvania	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/McAdoo%2C_Pennsylvania
pa	pa	O	B-LOC	Pennsylvania	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pennsylvania
.	O	O	#
definition	O	O	O
credit	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
debit	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
february;	O	O	O
2004	O	O	O
calendar	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nasir	nasir_shahabuddin	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
shahabuddin	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
kansas	kansas_city	O	B-LOC	Kansas_city	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kansas_city
city	O	O	I-LOC
star	O	O	O
horoscope	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tom	tom_goodman	O	B-PER	Tom_Goodman-Hill	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tom_Goodman-Hill
goodman	O	O	I-PER
attorney	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
antique-directory	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
saguaro	saguaro_park	O	B-LOC	Saguaro_National_Park	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Saguaro_National_Park
park	O	O	I-LOC
in	O	O	O
scottsdale;	scottsdale;_az	O	B-LOC	Scottsdale,_Arizona	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scottsdale%2C_Arizona
az	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
vt	vt	O	B-LOC	Vermont	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vermont
basketball	O	O	O
playoffs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ghanaimage	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bmx	O	O	O
bikesale	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
teachers	teachers_federal_credit_unio	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
federal	O	O	I-ORG
credit	O	O	I-ORG
unio	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
powerful;	O	O	O
magic;	O	O	O
real	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
project	project_healthy_beginnings	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
healthy	O	O	I-ORG
beginnings	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
pool	O	O	O
gifts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
acetylthiocholine	O	O	O
iodide	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hguitguhyhttityuyg	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
voice-over	O	O	O
casting	O	O	O
agency	O	O	O
miami	miami_beach	O	B-LOC	Miami_beach	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Miami_beach
beach	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
becoing	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
secured	O	O	O
debtor	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
final	O	O	O
fantasy	O	O	O
ganeshark	O	O	O
codes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
are	O	O	O
service	O	O	O
plans	O	O	O
worthwhile?	O	O	O
lcd	O	O	O
tv	O	O	O
service	O	O	O
plan	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
radigan	radigan_&	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
&	O	O	I-ORG
radigan;	radigan;	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
inc.	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gch	O	O	O
intranet	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fromage	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
du	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
nord	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
anissa	anissa_mcevoy	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
mcevoy	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
twinsouls	O	O	O
project	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
updatemsmoney	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
03	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
plugra	plugra	O	B-ORG	Plugra	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Plugra
butter	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rob	rob_bertrand	O	B-PER	Robert_Bertrand	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Bertrand
bertrand	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
contemporary	O	O	O
novelists	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
inuyasha	O	O	O
season	O	O	O
one	O	O	O
dvd	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
color	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
coral	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
movie	O	O	O
splicing	O	O	O
tape	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
monona	monona_catering	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
catering	O	O	I-ORG
madison	madison	O	B-LOC	Madison	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Madison
.	O	O	#
elsol95.co	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
picture	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
gimp	O	O	O
pulp	O	O	O
fiction	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
liverpool	liverpool	O	B-LOC	Liverpool	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Liverpool
accomodation	O	O	O
rent	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mystery	O	O	O
surrounds	O	O	O
death	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
guardsman	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sharp	sharp	O	B-ORG	Sharp	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sharp
vhs	O	O	O
full	O	O	O
size	O	O	O
camcorder	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
line	O	O	O
navy	navy	O	B-ORG	Navy	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Navy
ship	O	O	O
state	O	O	O
united	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chicago	chicago	O	B-LOC	Chicago	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicago
and	O	O	O
massage	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
girls	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
becky	becky	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
frogs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chilchota;	chilchota;	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
michoacan;	michoacan;	O	B-LOC	Michoacán	NONE
mexico	mexico	O	B-LOC	Mexico	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mexico
.	O	O	#
smashing	O	O	O
pumpkins	O	O	O
song	O	O	O
title	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mga	O	O	O
naging	O	O	O
talambuhay	O	O	O
ng	O	O	O
mga	O	O	O
pangulo	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
force	O	O	O
file	O	O	O
delete	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dv	O	O	O
com	O	O	O
calling	O	O	O
card	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bass	O	O	O
tabs	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
blessed	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
convert	O	O	O
ounces	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
quarts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
premium	O	O	O
choice	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
calling	O	O	O
card	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
training	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
great	O	O	O
dane	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
same	O	O	O
user	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
webmail	O	O	O
exchange	O	O	O
2000	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rs	O	O	O
muffers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
oriental	O	O	O
rugs	O	O	O
mn	mn	O	B-LOC	Mn	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mn
.	O	O	#
party	O	O	O
rental	O	O	O
stores	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
portland;	portland;_or	O	B-LOC	Portland,_Oregon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Portland%2C_Oregon
or	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
new	new_mexico	O	B-LOC	New_mexico	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_mexico
mexico	O	O	I-LOC
state	O	O	O
flage	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
edge	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
nowhere	O	O	O
band	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
valentines	O	O	O
birthday	O	O	O
ecards	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
a.	a.	O	B-PER	A.	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A.
e.	e._worsley	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
worsley	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
costume	O	O	O
shop	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
charlotter	charlotter	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
air	O	O	O
conditioning""	O	O	O
machine	O	O	O
used	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
deidra	deidra	O	B-PER	Deidra_Dionne	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deidra_Dionne
the	O	O	O
hot	O	O	O
toy	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
translation	O	O	O
from	O	O	O
french	O	O	O
till	O	O	O
arabic	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
kingsman	kingsman	O	B-ORG	Kingsman	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kingsman
firelplace	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cori	cori_werner_neustein	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
werner	O	O	I-PER
neustein	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
cross	O	O	O
creek	O	O	O
golf;	O	O	O
temecula	temecula	O	B-LOC	Temecula	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Temecula
.	O	O	#
motorbike	O	O	O
sound	O	O	O
file	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pillar	pillar	O	B-ORG	Pillar	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pillar
lyircs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
girls	O	O	O
find	O	O	O
guys	O	O	O
chat	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ici	ici_paints	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
paints	O	O	I-ORG
sinclair	O	O	O
3350n	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bites	O	O	O
from	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
loxosceles	O	O	O
laeta	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
school	O	O	O
border	O	O	O
clipart	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
main	O	O	O
idea	O	O	O
detail	O	O	O
lessons	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
children	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
seagrams	seagrams	O	B-ORG	Seagrams	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seagrams
liquior	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
albkkan	O	O	O
religion	O	O	O
gods	O	O	O
htm	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
paychiatric	O	O	O
flight	O	O	O
risk	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
outdoor	O	O	O
activity	O	O	O
ukraine	ukraine	O	B-LOC	Ukraine	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ukraine
.	O	O	#
covers	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
hard	O	O	O
hats	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rabbi	rabbi_nina_beth_cardin	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
nina	O	O	I-PER
beth	O	O	I-PER
cardin	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
dragon	O	O	O
or	O	O	O
microphone	O	O	O
or	O	O	O
compatibility	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
internet	O	O	O
explorer	O	O	O
cameo	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
find	O	O	O
business	O	O	O
by	O	O	O
adress	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
aleksey	aleksey	O	B-PER	Aleksey	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aleksey
gordienko	gordienko	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
treasure	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
david	david	O	B-PER	David	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/David
.	O	O	#
ls6	O	O	O
chevy	chevy	O	B-ORG	Chevy	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chevy
454	O	O	O
engine	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cory	cory_galliard	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
galliard	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
princess	O	O	O
landing	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dark	O	O	O
chocolate	O	O	O
fine	O	O	O
cooking	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ontario	ontario	O	B-LOC	Ontario	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ontario
partner	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
airpliance	airpliance	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
szakrt;90	O	O	O
fidesz	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
supportftp	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
air	O	O	O
tratic	O	O	O
control	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
abilene;	abilene;_texas""	O	B-LOC	Abilene,_Texas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abilene%2C_Texas
texas""	O	O	I-LOC
flower	O	O	O
shops	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
follow	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
leader	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mepi/uspto	O	O	O
middle	middle_east	O	B-LOC	Middle_east	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Middle_east
east	O	O	I-LOC
regional	O	O	O
customs	O	O	O
program	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
classic	O	O	O
rock	O	O	O
radios	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cheats	O	O	O
harry	O	O	O
potter	O	O	O
prisoner	O	O	O
ps2	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
autobusov	O	O	O
spoje	O	O	O
v	O	O	O
esk	O	O	O
republice	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
england	england	O	B-LOC	England	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/England
in	O	O	O
wwii	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sandia	sandia_high_school	O	B-ORG	Sandia_High_School	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sandia_High_School
high	O	O	I-ORG
school	O	O	I-ORG
spring	O	O	O
break	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
shamrock	O	O	O
shaped	O	O	O
cookware	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
visual	O	O	O
studio	O	O	O
jscript	O	O	O
debugger	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nov.20;1934	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
josef	josef_stalin	O	B-PER	Josef_stalin	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Josef_stalin
stalin	O	O	I-PER
life	life	O	B-PER	Life	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Life
.	O	O	#
brady	brady_book_company	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
book	O	O	I-ORG
company	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
katherine	katherine_mary_peyton	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
mary	O	O	I-PER
peyton	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
resort/tempe	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
deep	O	O	O
sea	O	O	O
fishing;	O	O	O
destin	destin	O	B-LOC	Destin,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Destin%2C_Florida
fl	fl	O	B-LOC	Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida
.	O	O	#
gateway;	gateway;	O	B-ORG	Gateway	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gateway
munster;	munster;	O	B-LOC	Munster	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Munster
indiana	indiana	O	B-LOC	Indiana	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indiana
.	O	O	#
alltel	alltel_arena	O	B-LOC	Alltel_Arena	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alltel_Arena
arena	O	O	I-LOC
calender	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
math	O	O	O
games:pythagorean	O	O	O
theorem	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
air	O	O	O
gate""	O	O	O
2004	O	O	O
ford	O	O	O
f250	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
firmware	O	O	O
updates	O	O	O
nec	O	O	O
2500	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
generic	O	O	O
drug	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
mevacor	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dequeen	dequeen	O	B-LOC	De_Queen,_Arkansas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/De_Queen%2C_Arkansas
public	O	O	O
wedding	O	O	O
announcements	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
boys	O	O	O
state	O	O	O
basketball	O	O	O
brackets	O	O	O
2004-2005	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
duvet	O	O	O
acoustic	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
setsuko	setsuko_shigetomi	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
shigetomi	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
ginja-love	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
unity	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
houston	houston	O	B-LOC	Houston	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Houston
mortgage	O	O	O
assistance	O	O	O
program	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
federal	federal	O	B-ORG	Federal	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Federal
mogel	mogel_corporation	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
corporation	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
babble	O	O	O
spanish	O	O	O
tanslations	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ovulation	O	O	O
prediction	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
pregnancy	O	O	O
questions	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
printable	O	O	O
cross	O	O	O
stitch	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
knowville	knowville_tn	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
tn	O	O	I-LOC
newspaper	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mp3/	O	O	O
digital	O	O	O
camera	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
examples	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
complex	O	O	O
sentence	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
poem	O	O	O
analyzation	O	O	O
""to	O	O	O
his	O	O	O
coy	O	O	O
mistress	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
atlant	O	O	O
weatjer	O	O	O
channel	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hockey	O	O	O
prospects	O	O	O
showcase	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
power	O	O	O
[point	O	O	O
viewer	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
river	O	O	O
walk	O	O	O
restuarnats	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
san	san_antonio	O	B-LOC	San_antonio	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/San_antonio
antonio	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
faq	O	O	O
site:j3w0.com	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
passport	O	O	O
airs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
marina	O	O	O
southern	southern_illinois	O	B-LOC	Southern_Illinois	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Southern_Illinois
illinois	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
ballot	O	O	O
now	O	O	O
voting	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
buy	O	O	O
aciphex	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
advantage	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
car	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
rental	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
australia	australia	O	B-LOC	Australia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Australia
.	O	O	#
salary	O	O	O
emt	O	O	O
offshore	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
baxley	baxley_georgia	O	B-LOC	Baxley,_Georgia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baxley%2C_Georgia
georgia	O	O	I-LOC
youth	O	O	O
homes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cooperative	O	O	O
apartments	O	O	O
association	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
brooklyn	brooklyn	O	B-LOC	Brooklyn	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brooklyn
.	O	O	#
overseas	O	O	O
cost	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
living	O	O	O
calculator	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tax	O	O	O
free	O	O	O
munisable	O	O	O
bonds	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
liu	liu_cwis_cwp_library	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
cwis	O	O	I-LOC
cwp	O	O	I-LOC
library	O	O	I-LOC
workshop	O	O	O
cittur	O	O	O
htlm	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
artic	artic_cat	O	B-ORG	Artic_Cat	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artic_Cat
cat	O	O	I-ORG
snowmobile	O	O	O
dealers	O	O	O
new	new_hampshire	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
hampshire	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
stoney	stoney_hollow_road	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
hollow	O	O	I-LOC
road	O	O	I-LOC
cabot	cabot_pa	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
pa	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
joaquin	joaquin_neypes	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
neypes	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
limescale	O	O	O
pics	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
robert	robert_perk	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
perk	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
los	los_angeles	O	B-LOC	Los_angeles	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Los_angeles
angeles	O	O	I-LOC
japan	japan	O	B-LOC	Japan	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Japan
golf	O	O	O
tour	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ms	O	O	O
access	O	O	O
aggregate	O	O	O
functions	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
official	O	O	O
anchorman	O	O	O
website	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pablo	pablo	O	B-PER	Pablo	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pablo
columbia	columbia	O	B-LOC	Columbia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Columbia
cartel	O	O	O
cocaine	O	O	O
pitcures	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
automotive	O	O	O
marketing	O	O	O
magazine	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
club	club	O	B-LOC	Club	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Club
24exercise	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bagger	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
toro	O	O	O
model	O	O	O
number20016	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
calories	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
patatoes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
filing	O	O	O
taxws	O	O	O
online	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
eliminazione	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
barriere	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
architettoniche	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cheap	O	O	O
hotel	O	O	O
adelaide	adelaide	O	B-LOC	Adelaide	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Adelaide
language:en	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
current	O	O	O
links	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dressy	O	O	O
statin	O	O	O
pump	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
map	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
kingston;	kingston;	O	B-LOC	Kingston,_Ontario	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kingston%2C_Ontario
ontario;	ontario;	O	B-LOC	Ontario	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ontario
canada	canada	O	B-LOC	Canada	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canada
.	O	O	#
arthur	arthur_conway	O	B-PER	Arthur_Conway	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arthur_Conway
conway	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
local	O	O	O
newspaper""	O	O	O
""pembroke	""pembroke_pines	O	B-ORG	Pembroke_pines	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pembroke_pines
pines	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
grams	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
ounce	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
shoe	O	O	O
redemption	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lisreplacment	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
psikologi	O	O	O
pendidikan	O	O	O
dalam	O	O	O
al-quran	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
outdoor	O	O	O
tool	O	O	O
sheds	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mature	O	O	O
timber	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cxc	cxc	O	B-ORG	CXC	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/CXC
examination	O	O	O
timetable	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
school	O	O	O
closings	O	O	O
washignton	washignton_dc	O	B-LOC	Washington,_D.C.	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Washington%2C_D.C.
dc	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
fournisseur	O	O	O
matriel	O	O	O
paramdical	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pictures	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
food	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
sulu	sulu	O	B-LOC	Sulu	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sulu
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
philippines	philippines	O	B-LOC	Philippines	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philippines
.	O	O	#
byy	O	O	O
wze	O	O	O
trzebinia	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
carefree	carefree_park	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
park	O	O	I-LOC
fl	fl	O	B-LOC	Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida
winter	winter_haven	O	B-LOC	Winter_Haven,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Winter_Haven%2C_Florida
haven	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
medical	O	O	O
jargon	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
staph	O	O	O
infection?	O	O	O
""murca?	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gkoisprfpde-d	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
epilepsy	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
coenzyme	O	O	O
q10	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
england-estate-london-real	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
replacement	O	O	O
light	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
vw	O	O	O
beetle	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
acadia/	acadia/_national_park	O	B-LOC	Acadia_National_Park	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acadia_National_Park
national	O	O	I-LOC
park	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
villa	O	O	O
hermosa	hermosa	O	B-LOC	Hermosa_Beach,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hermosa_Beach%2C_California	Hermosa	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hermosa
hermosa	hermosa_beach	O	B-LOC
beach	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
real	O	O	O
estate	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
hamden	hamden_ct	O	B-LOC	Hamden,_Connecticut	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hamden%2C_Connecticut
ct	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
diagram	O	O	O
water	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
robert	robert_burns	O	B-PER	Robert_Burns	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Burns
burns	O	O	I-PER
a	O	O	O
red	O	O	O
red	O	O	O
rose	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
poetryoffthepage	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
microstation	O	O	O
v8	O	O	O
problem	O	O	O
macro_acloud	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
experiment	O	O	O
relative	O	O	O
heat	O	O	O
capacity	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
afioh	O	O	O
hsw	O	O	O
col	O	O	O
item	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
florida	florida	O	B-LOC	Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida
transfer	O	O	O
vehicle	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
baseball	O	O	O
scotting	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
msr	O	O	O
backpack	O	O	O
stoves	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ronald	ronald_townsend	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
townsend	O	O	I-PER
biography	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
oak	oak_n'_brass	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
n'	O	O	I-ORG
brass	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
autobazar	autobazar_europa	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
europa	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
motorola	motorola	O	B-ORG	Motorola	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Motorola
bluetooth	O	O	O
base	O	O	O
unit	O	O	O
(mot-s9642)	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
swan	O	O	O
icons	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lifetimeof	O	O	O
rosaparks	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cortisone	O	O	O
injections	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
hip	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sata150	O	O	O
raid	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
overhead	O	O	O
transmission	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
electricity	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
jamaica	jamaica	O	B-LOC	Jamaica	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jamaica
.	O	O	#
football	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
play	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
designer	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
v3.0	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hodkins	O	O	O
tumor/heart	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dutch	O	O	O
children	O	O	O
pictures	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
real	O	O	O
estate	O	O	O
college	college_place;wa	O	B-LOC	College_Place,_Washington	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/College_Place%2C_Washington
place;wa	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
nba	O	O	O
live	O	O	O
installation	O	O	O
key	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nebraska	nebraska	O	B-LOC	Nebraska	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nebraska
rv	O	O	O
insurance	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
advance	O	O	O
structure	O	O	O
technology	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
aehghfgghkfjmkj	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sacramento	sacramento	O	B-LOC	Sacramento	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sacramento
or	O	O	O
roseville	roseville	O	B-LOC	Roseville	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roseville
teen	O	O	O
(under	O	O	O
18)	O	O	O
nightclubs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
congressional	O	O	O
commite	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
alternative	O	O	O
fuel	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pay	O	O	O
scale	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
astronauts	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
1960s	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
newspapers	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
charlotte	charlotte_nc	O	B-LOC	Charlotte,_North_Carolina	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Charlotte%2C_North_Carolina
nc	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
bayan	bayan_medical_company	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
medical	O	O	I-ORG
company	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
load	O	O	O
levellers	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
trailers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
columbia	columbia_missouri	O	B-LOC	Columbia,_Missouri	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Columbia%2C_Missouri
missouri	O	O	I-LOC
1000	O	O	O
willow	O	O	O
ridge	O	O	O
roared	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
europe;	europe;	O	B-LOC	Europe	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Europe
weather	O	O	O
forecast	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
massanutten	massanutten_virginia	O	B-LOC	Massanutten,_Virginia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Massanutten%2C_Virginia
virginia	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
o-scale	O	O	O
track	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
car	O	O	O
rentals	O	O	O
tel	tel_aviv	O	B-LOC	Tel_aviv	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tel_aviv
aviv	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
modern	O	O	O
""fireplace	O	O	O
cabinets""	O	O	O
around	O	O	O
fireplace	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
afp	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
iftim	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
find	O	O	O
words	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
kill	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
mockingbird	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lewis	lewis	O	B-PER	Lewis	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lewis
floorwax	floorwax	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
denver	denver	O	B-LOC	Denver	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Denver
radio	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
schol	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
dietician	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
play	O	O	O
seanc	O	O	O
from	O	O	O
greece	O	O	O
lighting	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
luxury	O	O	O
villas	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
rent	O	O	O
marbella	marbella	O	B-LOC	Marbella	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marbella
.	O	O	#
driver	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
scanner	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
plustek	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
pour	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
xp	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
vahid	vahid_tarokh	O	B-PER	Vahid_Tarokh	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vahid_Tarokh
tarokh	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
commercial	O	O	O
proterty	O	O	O
management	O	O	O
memphis	memphis_tenn	O	B-LOC	Memphis,_Tennessee	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Memphis%2C_Tennessee
tenn	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
mpm1stresults	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bahrain	bahrain	O	B-LOC	Bahrain	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bahrain
to	O	O	O
tehran	tehran	O	B-LOC	Tehran	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tehran
by	O	O	O
ferry	O	O	O
boat	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pictures	O	O	O
whit	O	O	O
flores	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
los	los_angeles	O	B-LOC	Los_angeles	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Los_angeles
angeles	O	O	I-LOC
county	O	O	O
fair	O	O	O
horse	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dave	dave_scadden	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
scadden	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
uses	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
a4	O	O	O
size	O	O	O
paper	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
canadian	O	O	O
apprenticeship	O	O	O
programs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
madison	madison_ave	O	B-LOC	Madison_ave	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Madison_ave
ave	O	O	I-LOC
income	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
characteristics	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
1964	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
catowomenclothe	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
spaghetti	O	O	O
seasoning	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ati	O	O	O
radeon	O	O	O
9800	O	O	O
pro	O	O	O
256	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
auto	O	O	O
repossessed	O	O	O
how	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
get	O	O	O
it	O	O	O
back	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
crack-poland	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
break_____donne	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ryan	ryan_michael_dawson	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
michael	O	O	I-PER
dawson	O	O	I-PER
lebo	O	O	O
kansas	kansas	O	B-LOC	Kansas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kansas
.	O	O	#
nappy	O	O	O
jeans	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bexar	bexar_county	O	B-LOC	Bexar_County	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bexar_County
county	O	O	I-LOC
surveys	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
martinsburg	martinsburg_wv	O	B-LOC	Martinsburg,_West_Virginia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Martinsburg%2C_West_Virginia
wv	O	O	I-LOC
beauty	O	O	O
shop	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
home	O	O	O
how-to	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alginates	O	O	O
as	O	O	O
suspending	O	O	O
agent	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
britney	britney_spears	O	B-PER	Britney_spears	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Britney_spears
spears	O	O	I-PER
index	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
expressio	O	O	O
unius	O	O	O
doctrine	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
super	O	O	O
kid	O	O	O
java	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
boces	O	O	O
workshops	O	O	O
""albany	""albany	O	B-LOC	Albany,_New_York	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Albany%2C_New_York
new	new_york	O	B-LOC	New_York	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_York
york	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
clipart	O	O	O
cleaning	O	O	O
house	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
event	O	O	O
viewer	O	O	O
application	O	O	O
log	O	O	O
error	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
canada	canada	O	B-LOC	Canada	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canada
post	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
rates/postage	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lights	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
liberty	O	O	O
tour	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
american	american_cleaners	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
cleaners	O	O	I-ORG
-	O	O	O
st.	st._louiw	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
louiw	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
does	O	O	O
amber	O	O	O
alert	O	O	O
acutally	O	O	O
work?	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ornamental	O	O	O
crab	O	O	O
trees	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
britney	britney_spears	O	B-PER	Britney_spears	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Britney_spears
spears	O	O	I-PER
199	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
eger	O	O	O
gygymasszr	O	O	O
tanfolyam	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
elenco	O	O	O
die	O	O	O
governatori	O	O	O
della	O	O	O
germania	germania	O	B-LOC	Germania	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Germania
.	O	O	#
grandi	O	O	O
domaini	O	O	O
it	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
col	col	O	B-PER	Col	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Col
bob	bob_day	O	B-PER	Bob_Day	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bob_Day
day	O	O	I-PER
medal	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
honor	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
at&t	at&t	O	B-ORG	At&t	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/At%26t
cell	O	O	O
ohone	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
marianna;	marianna;	O	B-LOC	Marianna,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marianna%2C_Florida
fl	O	O	O
vocational	O	O	O
schools	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
snape's	snape's	O	B-PER	Severus_Snape	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Severus_Snape
souity	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cranelakes	cranelakes	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
loyola	loyola_colleged	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
colleged	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
under	O	O	O
cabnet	O	O	O
mount	O	O	O
paper	O	O	O
towel	O	O	O
holder	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ohio	O	O	O
akc	akc_kennel_club	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
kennel	O	O	I-ORG
club	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
how	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
install	O	O	O
neww	O	O	O
electric	O	O	O
circuit	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dukenukem	O	O	O
full	O	O	O
version	O	O	O
download	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
motor	O	O	O
rama	rama	O	B-PER	Rama	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rama
in	O	O	O
dallas	dallas	O	B-LOC	Dallas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dallas
.	O	O	#
satellite	O	O	O
beacon	O	O	O
frequencies	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
angela	angela	O	B-PER	Angela	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Angela
perry""	O	O	O
engaged	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
condaleesa	condaleesa_rice	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
rice	O	O	I-PER
photo	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pip	O	O	O
exporter	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
large	O	O	O
awg	awg	O	B-ORG	AWG	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/AWG
crimpers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
illegal	O	O	O
fighting	O	O	O
mpegs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bfdeath;com	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
digital	O	O	O
fact	O	O	O
book	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
radm	O	O	O
robert	robert_conway	O	B-PER	Robert_Conway	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Conway
conway	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
metal	O	O	O
wind	O	O	O
chimes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ati	O	O	O
radeon	O	O	O
rx9550	O	O	O
se	O	O	O
td128	O	O	O
driver	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
real	O	O	O
ringtones	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
verizon	verizon	O	B-ORG	Verizon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Verizon
cell	O	O	O
phones	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
anatomy	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
landfill	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
embassy	embassy_of_norway	O	B-ORG	Embassy_of_Norway	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Embassy_of_Norway
of	O	O	I-ORG
norway	O	O	I-ORG
-	O	O	O
tanzania	tanzania	O	B-LOC	Tanzania	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tanzania
.	O	O	#
giuliani	giuliani_capital_advisors.	O	B-ORG	Giuliani_Partners	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Giuliani_Partners
capital	O	O	I-ORG
advisors.	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
fifty	O	O	O
five	O	O	O
year	O	O	O
old	O	O	O
wives	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
volleybal	O	O	O
camp	O	O	O
'university	'university_of_connecticut'	O	B-LOC	University_Of_Connecticut	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/University_Of_Connecticut
of	O	O	I-LOC
connecticut'	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
article	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
family	O	O	O
communication	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
al	O	O	O
shiiha	O	O	O
rituals	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
thinking	O	O	O
strategies	O	O	O
four	O	O	O
block	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alska	alska	O	B-LOC	Alaska	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alaska
fighting	O	O	O
championship	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
levasole(levamisole	O	O	O
hydrochloride)	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
norcal	norcal	O	B-LOC	Norcal	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Norcal
pet	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
buildings	O	O	O
with	O	O	O
passive	O	O	O
cooling	O	O	O
systems	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
detroit	detroit	O	B-LOC	Detroit	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Detroit
police	O	O	O
officer	O	O	O
sentenced	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
picture	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
decorated	O	O	O
cake	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
township	township_of_wilmerding	O	B-LOC	Wilmerding,_Pennsylvania	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wilmerding%2C_Pennsylvania
of	O	O	I-LOC
wilmerding	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
numismatics	numismatics_internatioinal	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
internatioinal	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
exercise	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
get	O	O	O
fatter	O	O	O
legs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
condoleeza	condoleeza_rice	O	B-PER	Condoleeza_Rice	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Condoleeza_Rice
rice	O	O	I-PER
pciture	O	O	O
reviewing	O	O	O
troops	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
error	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
""401""	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
""&""	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
modal	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
irs	irs	O	B-ORG	Irs	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irs
and	O	O	O
student	O	O	O
loand	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
napolian	O	O	O
tomato	O	O	O
sauce	O	O	O
recipe	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
property	O	O	O
consultants	O	O	O
real	O	O	O
estate	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rower	O	O	O
zellers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cochiseconsultancyinc	cochiseconsultancyinc	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
mardave	mardave_corp	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
corp	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
oncology;dover;nh	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
soapstone	O	O	O
price	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
car	O	O	O
ferry	O	O	O
provincetown	provincetown	O	B-LOC	Provincetown	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Provincetown
to	O	O	O
boston	boston	O	B-LOC	Boston	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Boston
.	O	O	#
eedspacenasa	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
accountants	O	O	O
tulsa	tulsa	O	B-LOC	Tulsa	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tulsa
.	O	O	#
greetings	O	O	O
sounds	O	O	O
download	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
navy	O	O	O
seahawk	O	O	O
helicopters	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
easy	O	O	O
go	O	O	O
usb	O	O	O
2.0	O	O	O
ide	O	O	O
adapter	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
computer	O	O	O
e-mails	O	O	O
notifiers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
michael	michael_w_smith	O	B-PER	Michael_W_Smith	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michael_W_Smith
w	O	O	I-PER
smith	O	O	I-PER
friends	O	O	O
lyrics	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
q-see	q-see	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
baby	O	O	O
monitor	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
template	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
rejection	O	O	O
letter	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
applicant	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
places	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
interest	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
cheshire	cheshire_england	O	B-LOC	Cheshire	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cheshire
england	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
medical	O	O	O
evaluation	O	O	O
board	board	O	B-ORG	Board	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Board
fort	fort_hood	O	B-LOC	Fort_hood	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fort_hood
hood	O	O	I-LOC
texas	texas	O	B-LOC	Texas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Texas
.	O	O	#
discount	O	O	O
duramax	O	O	O
diesel	O	O	O
upgrade	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
boston	O	O	O
terrior	O	O	O
puppies;	O	O	O
oklahoma	oklahoma	O	B-LOC	Oklahoma	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oklahoma
.	O	O	#
mayberry	O	O	O
black	O	O	O
forest	O	O	O
ham	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cd	O	O	O
vs	O	O	O
cdrw	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
argo	argo_high_school	O	B-ORG	Argo_Community_High_School	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Argo_Community_High_School
high	O	O	I-ORG
school	O	O	I-ORG
summit	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mineralsbyname	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mens	O	O	O
""dragon""	O	O	O
leather	O	O	O
coat	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bardonecchia/italy/hotels	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
delivered	O	O	O
meds	O	O	O
3.57	O	O	O
phem	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
faq	O	O	O
site:-vf_.com	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fifties	O	O	O
prom	O	O	O
gowns	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
passenger	O	O	O
1904	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sea	O	O	O
same	O	O	O
street	O	O	O
games	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fairwayfinancialservices	fairwayfinancialservices	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
.	O	O	#
canyon	canyon_lake	O	B-LOC	Canyon_Lake	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Canyon_Lake
lake	O	O	I-LOC
rapid	rapid_city;	O	B-LOC	Rapid_City,_South_Dakota	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rapid_City%2C_South_Dakota
city;	O	O	I-LOC
south	south_dakota	O	B-LOC	South_dakota	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_dakota
dakota	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
no	O	O	O
car	car	O	B-LOC	Car	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Car
insurance	O	O	O
law	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
california	california	O	B-LOC	California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/California
.	O	O	#
learn	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
traditional	O	O	O
lebonese	O	O	O
dance	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ap	O	O	O
human	O	O	O
geography	O	O	O
tests	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dannish	O	O	O
cookies	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
accomodation	O	O	O
near	O	O	O
daventry	daventry_uk	O	B-LOC	Daventry_(UK_Parliament_constituency)	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Daventry_%28UK_Parliament_constituency%29
uk	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
labview	O	O	O
formula	O	O	O
node	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
villa	villa_park_elementary	O	B-ORG	Villa_Park,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Villa_Park%2C_California
park	O	O	I-ORG
elementary	O	O	I-ORG
api	O	O	O
scores	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
orange	orange_county	O	B-LOC	Orange_County,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orange_County%2C_California
county	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
federal	O	O	O
goverment	O	O	O
status	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
verio	O	O	O
trouble	O	O	O
site	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
kris	kris	O	B-PER	Kris	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kris
howe""	O	O	O
nebraska	nebraska	O	B-LOC	Nebraska	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nebraska
.	O	O	#
fork	O	O	O
lift	O	O	O
training	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
north	north_carolina	O	B-LOC	North_carolina	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_carolina
carolina	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
family	O	O	O
as	O	O	O
unit	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
definition	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
comprehensive	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
miller	miller_brewery	O	B-ORG	Miller_Brewing_Company	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Miller_Brewing_Company
brewery	O	O	I-ORG
wallpaper	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mp3	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
ericsson	ericsson	O	B-ORG	Ericsson	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ericsson
gsm	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
metabolism	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
glucose	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
priceline	priceline	O	B-ORG	Priceline	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Priceline
travel	O	O	O
insurance	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
costco	costco	O	B-ORG	Costco	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Costco
jewellery	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
fire	O	O	O
red	O	O	O
leaf	O	O	O
green	O	O	O
version	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
harlan	harlan_electric	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
electric	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
locate	O	O	O
book	O	O	O
stores	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
london	london	O	B-LOC	London	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/London
.	O	O	#
hind	O	O	O
shorts	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
colorado	colorado	O	B-LOC	Colorado	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Colorado
fishing	O	O	O
guide	O	O	O
trout	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ford	O	O	O
4.9	O	O	O
i6	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pistol	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
florida	florida	O	B-LOC	Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida
.	O	O	#
michael	michael_vick	O	B-PER	Michael_vick	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michael_vick
vick	O	O	I-PER
shoes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mille	mille_lacs	O	B-ORG	Mille_Lacs	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mille_Lacs
lacs	O	O	I-ORG
band	O	O	O
training	O	O	O
grants	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
esthetician	O	O	O
uniforms	O	O	O
europe	europe	O	B-LOC	Europe	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Europe
.	O	O	#
panasonic	panasonic	O	B-ORG	Panasonic	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Panasonic
allure	O	O	O
leather	O	O	O
cases	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
city	city_of_surrey_fire_dept	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
of	O	O	I-ORG
surrey	O	O	I-ORG
fire	O	O	I-ORG
dept	O	O	I-ORG
rules	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
used	O	O	O
oil	O	O	O
tanks	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
can	O	O	O
you	O	O	O
have	O	O	O
an	O	O	O
overcast	O	O	O
sky	O	O	O
with	O	O	O
stratus	O	O	O
fractus	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nicomponte	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
celebrity	O	O	O
forum	O	O	O
foot	foot_hill_college	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
hill	O	O	I-ORG
college	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
activ	O	O	O
directory	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
navy	O	O	O
physical	O	O	O
security	O	O	O
manual	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ken	ken_owyang	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
owyang	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
sweetheart	O	O	O
lyrics	O	O	O
u2	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mil-prf-23699f	O	O	O
msds	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
superbowl	O	O	O
thirty	O	O	O
nine	O	O	O
commerative	O	O	O
hummels	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
state	O	O	O
rankings	O	O	O
elementary	O	O	O
math	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pain	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
inconvenience	O	O	O
settlement;	O	O	O
scar	O	O	O
settlement	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
broumovsky	O	O	O
zpravodaj	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
clark	clark_county_ohio	O	B-LOC	Clark_County,_Ohio	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clark_County%2C_Ohio
county	O	O	I-LOC
ohio	O	O	I-LOC
assessor	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
achitecture	O	O	O
ove-arup	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ford	O	O	O
diesel	O	O	O
v	O	O	O
belt	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
travel	O	O	O
agency	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
brasil	brasil	O	B-LOC	Brasil	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brasil
.	O	O	#
chevy	O	O	O
s-10	O	O	O
heater	O	O	O
core	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
okoichovice	O	O	O
cz	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
curacao	curacao_sfea_acquarium	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
sfea	O	O	I-LOC
acquarium	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
osu/okc	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
oklahoma	oklahoma	O	B-LOC	Oklahoma	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oklahoma
citynursing	O	O	O
program	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
czsci	O	O	O
do	O	O	O
pralek	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
map	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
saskatoon	saskatoon	O	B-LOC	Saskatoon	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Saskatoon
.	O	O	#
panama	panama_city;_fla	O	B-LOC	Panama_City,_Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Panama_City%2C_Florida
city;	O	O	I-LOC
fla	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
color	O	O	O
pages;	O	O	O
dragons	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
central	central_dispatch	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
dispatch	O	O	I-ORG
houston	houston_texas	O	B-LOC	Houston_texas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Houston_texas
texas	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
download	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
him	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
surface	O	O	O
transportation	O	O	O
board	O	O	O
searches	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gheuihttuhurhutirhjt	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dominecker	O	O	O
rooster	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
taking	O	O	O
back	O	O	O
sunday""	O	O	O
lyrics	O	O	O
i	O	O	O
wanna	O	O	O
hear	O	O	O
you	O	O	O
scream	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
spread	O	O	O
4u	O	O	O
live	O	O	O
web	O	O	O
cams	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dragonfly	O	O	O
hunting	O	O	O
tequneques	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
american	american_airline	O	B-ORG	American_airline	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_airline
airline	O	O	I-ORG
telephone	O	O	O
#	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bernsworth	bernsworth_inn	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
inn	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
chair	O	O	O
rails	O	O	O
cutting	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
best	best_western	O	B-ORG	Best_Western	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Best_Western
western	O	O	I-ORG
meadow	meadow_acres	O	B-LOC	Meadow_Acres,_Wyoming	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Meadow_Acres%2C_Wyoming
acres	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
stretto	O	O	O
fugue	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rhode	rhode_island	O	B-LOC	Rhode_island	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rhode_island
island	O	O	I-LOC
trailer	O	O	O
park	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
kelli	kelli_maccord	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
maccord	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
apex	O	O	O
4800-g2-p4	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
post	post_office	O	B-ORG	Post_office	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Post_office
office	O	O	I-ORG
-	O	O	O
denver	denver	O	B-LOC	Denver	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Denver
.	O	O	#
repice	O	O	O
potato	O	O	O
cake	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cheap	O	O	O
car	O	O	O
dvd	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gay	O	O	O
male	O	O	O
lovers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
leprosy	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
bible	O	O	O
times	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
copper	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
facial	O	O	O
cream	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
seccio	O	O	O
n	O	O	O
amarilla	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mcdonalds	mcdonalds	O	B-ORG	Mcdonalds	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mcdonalds
and	O	O	O
pizza	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
flash	O	O	O
game	O	O	O
machine	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
ashleys	ashleys	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
menu	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
plotting	O	O	O
scale	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
a	O	O	O
walk	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
temecula	temecula_california	O	B-LOC	Temecula_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Temecula_California
california	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
acculab	O	O	O
crd-150;	O	O	O
recalibrate	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
boeing	O	O	O
667	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chinese	O	O	O
wedding	O	O	O
music	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
odzyskiwanie	O	O	O
mienia	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
property	O	O	O
values	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
rhode	rhode_island	O	B-LOC	Rhode_island	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rhode_island
island	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
rare	O	O	O
apple	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
criminal	O	O	O
records	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
santa	santa_cruz	O	B-LOC	Santa_Cruz_County,_Arizona	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Santa_Cruz_County%2C_Arizona
cruz	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
enigma	O	O	O
return	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
innocence	O	O	O
download	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
thoreau/transcendentalism	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
a.	O	O	O
zahner	zahner	O	B-PER	Zahner	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zahner
architectural	O	O	O
metal	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sae	O	O	O
tn	O	O	O
beta	O	O	O
pictures	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
respiratory	O	O	O
response:	O	O	O
bronchiole	O	O	O
asthma	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
antecedentes	O	O	O
de	O	O	O
presupuesto	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
michigan	michigan	O	B-LOC	Michigan	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Michigan
car	O	O	O
dealers	O	O	O
websites	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
air	O	O	O
intake	O	O	O
heater	O	O	O
wire	O	O	O
diagram	O	O	O
dodge	O	O	O
ram	O	O	O
3500	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
celtic	O	O	O
tribal	O	O	O
armband	O	O	O
tattoo	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
unn	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
advance	O	O	O
technology	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dial	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
start	O	O	O
up	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cgx-171cca	O	O	O
yamaha	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tom	tom_bass_park;	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
bass	O	O	I-LOC
park;	O	O	I-LOC
houston;	houston;	O	B-LOC	Houston	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Houston
texas	texas	O	B-LOC	Texas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Texas
.	O	O	#
las	las_vegas	O	B-LOC	Las_vegas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Las_vegas
vegas	O	O	I-LOC
accomidations	O	O	O
cheap	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
amortizare	O	O	O
accelerata	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dollynight	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mckenzie	mckenzie	O	B-PER	Mackenzie_(surname)	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mackenzie_%28surname%29
trust	trust	O	B-ORG	Trust	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trust
.	O	O	#
continental	O	O	O
airlines	O	O	O
executive	O	O	O
bonus	O	O	O
program	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nature	O	O	O
centers	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
denver	denver	O	B-LOC	Denver	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Denver
.	O	O	#
targus	targus	O	B-ORG	Targus	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Targus
city	O	O	O
gear	O	O	O
tcg400	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chon	O	O	O
buri	O	O	O
buffalo	O	O	O
races	O	O	O
thailand	thailand	O	B-LOC	Thailand	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thailand
.	O	O	#
cuba's	O	O	O
recipes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mother-daughter	O	O	O
inspirational	O	O	O
quotes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
intel	intel	O	B-ORG	Intel	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Intel
and	O	O	O
82801db	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
(m)	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
ich4(-m)-ac	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
97	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
traslate	O	O	O
english	O	O	O
text	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
spanish	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
new	new_orleans_louisiana	O	B-LOC	New_Orleans	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Orleans
orleans	O	O	I-LOC
louisiana	O	O	I-LOC
channel	O	O	O
4	O	O	O
news	news	O	B-LOC	News	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/News
.	O	O	#
realtors	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
winterhaven	winterhaven	O	B-LOC	Winterhaven	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Winterhaven
florida	florida	O	B-LOC	Florida	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florida
.	O	O	#
morrowind:	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
philip	philip	O	B-PER	Philip	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Philip
and	O	O	O
""kotler's""	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
""4""	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
""c's	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
biographical	O	O	O
information	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
martin	martin_luther_king	O	B-PER	Martin_luther_king	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Martin_luther_king
luther	O	O	I-PER
king	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
potatoes	O	O	O
alaska	alaska	O	B-LOC	Alaska	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alaska
reference	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
number	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
messages""	O	O	O
organization	O	O	O
design	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cashew	O	O	O
juice	O	O	O
health	O	O	O
drink	O	O	O
singapore	singapore	O	B-LOC	Singapore	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Singapore
.	O	O	#
moma	moma_lombardi's	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
lombardi's	O	O	I-PER
long	long_island_ny	O	B-LOC	Long_Island	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Long_Island
island	O	O	I-LOC
ny	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
cultered	O	O	O
marble	O	O	O
top	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tomb	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
lucrezia	lucrezia_borgia	O	B-PER	Lucrezia_Borgia	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lucrezia_Borgia
borgia	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
rd	O	O	O
electronics/ru	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
real	O	O	O
estate	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
glen	glen	O	B-LOC	Glen	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glen
oaks;	oaks;	O	B-LOC	Oaks	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oaks
ny	ny	O	B-LOC	New_York	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_York
.	O	O	#
rattan	O	O	O
baskets	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
story	O	O	O
behind	O	O	O
toy	O	O	O
soldiers	O	O	O
-	O	O	O
eminem	eminem	O	B-PER	Eminem	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eminem
.	O	O	#
affordable	O	O	O
weddings	O	O	O
sites	O	O	O
durango	durango	O	B-LOC	Durango	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Durango
.	O	O	#
counseling	O	O	O
debt	O	O	O
fl	O	O	O
free	O	O	O
reduction	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
huston-tillotson	huston-tillotson	O	B-LOC	Huston-Tillotson	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Huston-Tillotson
college	O	O	O
music	O	O	O
department	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alexandra	alexandra_baryshnikov	O	B-PER	Alexandr_Baryshnikov	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexandr_Baryshnikov
baryshnikov	O	O	I-PER
gives	O	O	O
birth	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
msnstockquote	O	O	O
historical	O	O	O
data	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
how	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
build	O	O	O
metal	O	O	O
rockets	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
promotional	O	O	O
basketball	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
gametraining	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lebanese	O	O	O
beaities	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
celebreties	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
itbs	O	O	O
items	O	O	O
by	O	O	O
grade	O	O	O
level	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pictures	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
thermal	O	O	O
pollutants	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
motosport	motosport_outlet_inc	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
outlet	O	O	I-ORG
inc	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
brittan	brittan	O	B-LOC	Brittan	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brittan
rulers	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
1492	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chuck	chuck_and_e_and_cheese;	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
and	O	O	I-ORG
e	O	O	I-ORG
and	O	O	I-ORG
cheese;	O	O	I-ORG
and	O	O	I-ORG
rochester;	rochester;_and_ny	O	B-LOC	Rochester,_New_York	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rochester%2C_New_York
and	O	O	I-LOC
ny	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
picc	O	O	O
lines	O	O	O
certification	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
lowes	lowes_home_improvement	O	B-ORG	Lowes_home_improvement	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lowes_home_improvement
home	O	O	I-ORG
improvement	O	O	I-ORG
of	O	O	O
wilson	wilson	O	B-LOC	Wilson	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wilson
.	O	O	#
pennslyvania	pennslyvania	O	B-LOC	Pennslyvania	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pennslyvania
state	O	O	O
statutes	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
probate	O	O	O
process	O	O	O
pennsylvania	pennsylvania	O	B-LOC	Pennsylvania	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pennsylvania
.	O	O	#
dell	dell	O	B-ORG	Dell	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dell
elsalvador	elsalvador	O	B-LOC	El_Salvador	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/El_Salvador
.	O	O	#
photo	O	O	O
aginepi	O	O	O
light	O	O	O
lazer	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
first	O	O	O
women	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
olympics	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
father	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
happy	O	O	O
days	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
function	O	O	O
nucleoside	O	O	O
triphosphate	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
angel	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
show	O	O	O
called	O	O	O
angel	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
density;	O	O	O
mass	O	O	O
formula	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
for	O	O	O
sale	O	O	O
monkeys	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
michael	michael_veasey	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
veasey	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
dialysis	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
waiting	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
lists	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
uk	uk	O	B-LOC	Uk	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uk
.	O	O	#
tierras	O	O	O
del	O	O	O
sieclos	O	O	O
xii	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
buick	buick	O	B-ORG	Buick	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Buick
dealer;	O	O	O
tappahannock	tappahannock	O	B-LOC	Tappahannock	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tappahannock
.	O	O	#
second	second_""chance_pbgv""_rescue	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
""chance	O	O	I-ORG
pbgv""	O	O	I-ORG
rescue	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
naturally	O	O	O
occurring	O	O	O
retiremen	O	O	O
community	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
mercury	O	O	O
sable	O	O	O
interior	O	O	O
color	O	O	O
options	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
megan	megan_mulvaney	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
mulvaney	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
city	O	O	O
map	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
colorado	colorado	O	B-LOC	Colorado	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Colorado
.	O	O	#
richmond	richmond_hill_united_church	O	B-ORG	Richmond_Hill_United_Church	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richmond_Hill_United_Church
hill	O	O	I-ORG
united	O	O	I-ORG
church	O	O	I-ORG
ontario	ontario	O	B-LOC	Ontario	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ontario
.	O	O	#
masage	O	O	O
para	O	O	O
la	O	O	O
ceulitis	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
robter	robter_jones	O	B-PER	Robert_Jones	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Jones
jones	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
central	central_michigan_university_school_of	O	B-ORG	Central_Michigan_University	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Central_Michigan_University
michigan	O	O	I-ORG
university	O	O	I-ORG
school	O	O	I-ORG
of	O	O	I-ORG
music	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
math	O	O	O
piping	O	O	O
problem	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
afgacamera	O	O	O
driver	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
pegamento	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
pvc	O	O	O
tangit	O	O	O
mx	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
geotechicnal	O	O	O
analysis	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
apple	O	O	O
pie""	O	O	O
raisins	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cedar	cedar_lake_memorial_park	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
lake	O	O	I-LOC
memorial	O	O	I-LOC
park	O	O	I-LOC
campground	campground	O	B-LOC	Campground	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Campground
.	O	O	#
career	O	O	O
involving	O	O	O
anatomy	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
dhcp	O	O	O
overview	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
honduran	honduran	O	B-LOC	Honduran	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Honduran
retirement	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
love	O	O	O
freaks	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
burglar	O	O	O
prowl	O	O	O
movie	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cheerleading	O	O	O
doll	O	O	O
icons	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tracy	tracy_austiin	O	B-PER	Tracy_Austin	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tracy_Austin
austiin	O	O	I-PER
tennis	O	O	O
star	star	O	B-PER	Star	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Star
.	O	O	#
mobile	O	O	O
physical	O	O	O
therapy;	O	O	O
raleigh;	raleigh;	O	B-LOC	Raleigh	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Raleigh
nc	nc	O	B-LOC	Nc	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nc
.	O	O	#
boys	O	O	O
""knee	O	O	O
high""	O	O	O
socks	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cory	cory_horth	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE
horth	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
double	O	O	O
wedding	O	O	O
ring	O	O	O
quilt	O	O	O
pattern	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
print	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
cel	O	O	O
mai	O	O	O
bun	O	O	O
avion	O	O	O
de	O	O	O
vanatoare	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
histiological	O	O	O
pics	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
osteoporosis	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
countryclulb	countryclulb	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
of	O	O	O
fairfax.	fairfax.	O	B-LOC	Fairfax,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fairfax%2C_California
.	O	O	#
california	california	O	B-LOC	California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/California
police	O	O	O
auction	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
live	O	O	O
music	O	O	O
prices	O	O	O
new	new_york	O	B-LOC	New_york	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_york
york	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
free	O	O	O
celeb	O	O	O
picsl	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
can	O	O	O
you	O	O	O
track	O	O	O
location	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
cell	O	O	O
phone	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
moving	O	O	O
pagefile	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
null	O	O	O
pointer	O	O	O
passed	O	O	O
stub	O	O	O
windows	O	O	O
media	O	O	O
player	O	O	O
10	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bacxkgrounds	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
safety	O	O	O
ratings	O	O	O
cribs	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
complex	O	O	O
environment	O	O	O
where	O	O	O
this	O	O	O
industry	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
tuturing	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
microsoft	microsoft	O	B-ORG	Microsoft	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microsoft
power	O	O	O
point	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
screaming	O	O	O
trees	O	O	O
punkrock	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rosehip	O	O	O
picture	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
creech	O	O	O
bill;	O	O	O
article	O	O	O
115-c	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
belsoie	belsoie	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
formal	O	O	O
wear	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
though	O	O	O
rough	O	O	O
bred	O	O	O
characteristics	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
moody	moody_blues	O	B-ORG	Moody_Blues	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moody_Blues
blues	O	O	I-ORG
days	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
passed	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
dawn	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bbc_readysteadycook	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sholaderma	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
nation	O	O	O
expects	O	O	O
ignorant	O	O	O
free	O	O	O
expects	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bj	bj_penn	O	B-PER	Bj_penn	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bj_penn
penn	O	O	I-PER
pics	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
condo	O	O	O
rentals	O	O	O
at	O	O	O
eagle	eagle_pointe	O	B-LOC	NONE	NONE
pointe	O	O	I-LOC
in	O	O	O
indiana	indiana	O	B-LOC	Indiana	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Indiana
.	O	O	#
tripp	tripp_county	O	B-LOC	Tripp_County	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tripp_County
county	O	O	I-LOC
catholics	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
canton	O	O	O
exhibitoin	O	O	O
china	china	O	B-LOC	China	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/China
.	O	O	#
silcon	O	O	O
dress	O	O	O
pads	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
open	O	O	O
doors""	O	O	O
foundation	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
emmit	emmit_smith	O	B-PER	Emmit_Smith	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Emmit_Smith
smith	O	O	I-PER
.	O	O	#
dale	dale_earnhardt_sr	O	B-PER	Dale_Earnhardt	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dale_Earnhardt
earnhardt	O	O	I-PER
sr	O	O	I-PER
wallpapers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
hdtv	O	O	O
buyers	O	O	O
guide	O	O	O
plasma	O	O	O
lcd	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
seafood	O	O	O
markets	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
hampton	hampton_roads_va	O	B-LOC	Hampton_Roads	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hampton_Roads
roads	O	O	I-LOC
va	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
annuaire	O	O	O
en	O	O	O
france	france	O	B-LOC	France	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/France
.	O	O	#
presonus	O	O	O
mp	O	O	O
20	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bought	O	O	O
copies	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
fair	O	O	O
grounds""	O	O	O
language:en	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
new	new_river_media_partners;	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
river	O	O	I-ORG
media	O	O	I-ORG
partners;	O	O	I-ORG
radford;	radford;	O	B-LOC	Radford	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Radford
vas	vas	O	B-ORG	Vas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vas
.	O	O	#
how	O	O	O
taget	O	O	O
stuff	O	O	O
formytrack	O	O	O
fone	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alazar	alazar_riverboat_casino	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
riverboat	O	O	I-ORG
casino	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
psd	O	O	O
informs	O	O	O
dfas	O	O	O
close	O	O	O
account	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
bed	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
breakfast	O	O	O
oklahoma	oklahoma_city	O	B-LOC	Oklahoma_city	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oklahoma_city
city	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
compare	O	O	O
mac	O	O	O
os	O	O	O
9	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
attachments	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
pgp	O	O	O
e-mail	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
toy	O	O	O
story	O	O	O
videio	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
newspaper	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
year	O	O	O
1977-1980	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
blue	blue_cross	O	B-ORG	Blue_Cross_and_Blue_Shield_Association	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blue_Cross_and_Blue_Shield_Association	The_Blue_Cross	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Blue_Cross
cross	O	O	I-ORG
blue	blue_shield	O	B-ORG
shield	O	O	I-ORG
compainion	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
northwest	northwest	O	B-LOC	Northwest	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Northwest
world	O	O	O
perks	O	O	O
#780-998-971	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chiropractic	chiropractic_associasion	O	B-ORG	American_Chiropractic_Association	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_Chiropractic_Association
associasion	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
roberts	roberts	O	B-PER	Roberts	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Roberts
company	company	O	B-ORG	Company	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Company
.	O	O	#
enigma	O	O	O
music	O	O	O
stile	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
search	O	O	O
mytle	O	O	O
beach	O	O	O
south	O	O	O
carolina	carolina	O	B-LOC	South_Carolina	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/South_Carolina
cruise	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
c3po	O	O	O
buddy	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
emulator	O	O	O
delta	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
local	O	O	O
maps	O	O	O
of	O	O	O
gatlinburg	gatlinburg	O	B-LOC	Gatlinburg	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gatlinburg
tn.	tn.	O	B-LOC	Tennessee	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tennessee
.	O	O	#
boat	O	O	O
accident	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
long	long_beach;_ca	O	B-LOC	Long_Beach,_California	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Long_Beach%2C_California
beach;	O	O	I-LOC
ca	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
glasscock	glasscock_county	O	B-LOC	Glasscock_County,_Texas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glasscock_County%2C_Texas
county	O	O	I-LOC
recorder	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
save	O	O	O
a	O	O	O
little	O	O	O
more	O	O	O
for	O	O	O
retirement	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
atv	O	O	O
knock	O	O	O
off	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
polyp	O	O	O
rene	O	O	O
tanke	O	O	O
trunks	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
chimo	O	O	O
pool	O	O	O
coquitlam	coquitlam	O	B-LOC	Coquitlam	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Coquitlam
.	O	O	#
realestate	O	O	O
in	in	O	B-LOC	In	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/In
il	il	O	B-LOC	Il	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Il
on	O	O	O
ebay	ebay	O	B-ORG	Ebay	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ebay
.	O	O	#
northeastfourwheelclub	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
barn	O	O	O
yard	O	O	O
baby	O	O	O
room	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
rrs	O	O	O
14:32.1	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
the	O	O	O
code	O	O	O
to	O	O	O
unlock	O	O	O
i95	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
alcohol	O	O	O
drug	O	O	O
prevention	O	O	O
parenting	O	O	O
curriculum	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
panama	panama	O	B-LOC	Panama	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Panama
city;fl	O	O	O
apartments	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
braza	braza_grill	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
grill	O	O	I-ORG
in	O	O	O
cleveland	cleveland	O	B-LOC	Cleveland	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleveland
.	O	O	#
italian	O	O	O
words	O	O	O
from	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
godfather	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
g	O	O	O
lista	O	O	O
wolsztajna	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
saxophone	O	O	O
player	O	O	O
weather	O	O	O
report	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
vu	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
et	O	O	O
and	O	O	O
entandu	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
roanoke	roanoke_neurological_associates	O	B-ORG	NONE	NONE
neurological	O	O	I-ORG
associates	O	O	I-ORG
.	O	O	#
cotton	O	O	O
knit	O	O	O
comfort	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
sjd	O	O	O
mu	O	O	O
no	O	O	O
ip	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
play	O	O	O
morrowind	O	O	O
the	O	O	O
elder	O	O	O
scrolls	O	O	O
three	O	O	O
on	O	O	O
internet	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
allen	allen_entrekin	O	B-PER	NONE	NONE	NONE	NONE
entrekin	O	O	I-PER
allen	allen_pennsylvania	O	B-LOC
pennsylvania	O	O	I-LOC
.	O	O	#
cheap	O	O	O
santa	O	O	O
suits	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
paris	paris	O	B-PER	Paris	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paris
hilton's	hilton's	O	B-PER	Paris_Hilton	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Paris_Hilton
phone	O	O	O
books	O	O	O
numbers	O	O	O
.	O	O	#
employment	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
aviano	aviano	O	B-LOC	Aviano	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aviano
italy	italy	O	B-LOC	Italy	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Italy
.	O	O	#
cargo	O	O	O
trailers	O	O	O
in	O	O	O
kansas	kansas	O	B-LOC	Kansas	http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kansas
.	O	O	#
